LEICESTERSHIRE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Such JJ I-NP I-PER O
Such JJ I-NP I-PER O
Butcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
reducing VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Australian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Tom NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
O'Gorman NNP I-NP I-PER O
dismiss VB I-VP O I-ORG
ex-England JJ I-NP I-MISC O
McCague NNP I-NP I-PER O
By IN I-PP O I-ORG
stumps NNS I-NP O I-ORG
CHAMPIONSHIP WDT B-NP I-MISC O
296 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Dale NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blenkiron NNP B-NP I-PER O
214 CD I-NP O I-ORG
McCague NNP I-NP I-PER O
108-3 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
429-7 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Butcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kersey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ratcliffe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bicknell NNP I-NP I-PER O
363 CD I-NP O I-ORG
197-8 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
W. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hegg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chesterfield NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
471 CD I-NP O I-ORG
T.O'Gorman JJ I-NP I-PER O
T. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
6-82 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bristol NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
190 CD I-NP O I-ORG
ASHES NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Ashes NNP I-NP I-MISC O
a SYM O O I-ORG
six-test JJ I-NP O I-ORG
starting VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Test NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP I-ORG O
four CD I-NP O I-LOC
English JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Minor NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Counties NNP I-NP I-ORG O
May NNP I-NP O I-LOC
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
Lord NNP I-NP I-LOC O
's POS I-NP I-LOC O
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
Arundel NNP I-NP I-LOC O
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
Northampton NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
First NNP I-NP O I-ORG
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
Lord NNP I-NP I-LOC O
's POS I-NP I-LOC O
May NNP I-NP O I-ORG
27-29 CD I-NP O I-ORG
days NNS I-NP O I-LOC
May NNP I-NP O I-PER
June NNP I-NP O I-ORG
5-9 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
First NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Birmingham NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
June NNP I-NP O I-ORG
11-13 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Lord NNP I-NP I-LOC O
's POS I-NP I-LOC O
Oxford NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Manchester NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
July NNP I-NP O I-ORG
24-28 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Fourth NNP I-NP O I-ORG
August NNP I-NP O I-LOC
August NNP I-NP O I-ORG
7-11 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Fifth NNP I-NP O I-ORG
August NNP I-NP O I-ORG
16-18 CD I-NP O I-ORG
August NNP I-NP O I-ORG
21-25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sixth NNP I-NP O I-ORG
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
SHEARER NN I-NP I-PER O
Platt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Platt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shearer NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
but CC O O I-LOC
Shearer NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Teddy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sheringham NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shearer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
basketball NN I-NP O I-LOC
47-47 CD I-ADVP O I-LOC
LITHUANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Cosmin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Contra NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mihai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tararache NNP I-NP I-PER O
Danius NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gleveckas NNP I-NP I-PER O
ROTOR NN I-NP I-ORG O
VOLGOGRAD NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Anatoly NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gorokhovsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lying VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Alania NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Volgograd NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BOXING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
PANAMA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
'S POS B-NP O I-ORG
ROBERTO NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
DURAN NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
FIGHTS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Panamanian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
boxing NN I-NP O I-ORG
" " O I-PER O
Hands NNS I-NP I-PER O
of IN I-PP I-PER O
Stone NNP I-NP I-PER O
" " O I-PER O
Duran JJ I-NP I-PER O
Duran NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
little-known JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Ariel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cruz NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
super JJ I-NP O I-ORG
middleweight NN I-NP O I-ORG
non-title NN I-NP O I-ORG
bout NN I-NP O I-ORG
Duran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Return NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
the DT I-NP I-MISC O
Legend NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Duran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Duran JJ I-NP I-PER O
Panamanian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Manzanares NNP I-NP I-PER O
Duran NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
" " O I-PER O
Macho NNP I-NP I-PER O
" " O I-PER O
Camacho NN I-NP I-PER O
Camacho NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Panamanian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Quarter-final JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Suwan JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
professional JJ I-NP O I-ORG
baseball NN I-NP O I-ORG
and CC O O I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Jan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kroslak NNP I-NP I-PER O
6-0 CD I-NP O I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
DETROIT NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
TORONTO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
TEXAS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CALIFORNIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
OAKLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
SEATTLE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CINCINNATI NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MONTREAL NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
PHILADELPHIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
PITTSBURGH NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kansas NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
City NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Minnesota NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
New NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
York NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Chicago NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
18 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Florida NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
TARANGO NNP I-NP I-PER O
O'BRIEN NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
SPRING NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TWIN NNP I-NP O I-ORG
UPSETS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
UNDER IN I-PP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Wimbledon NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Wimbledon NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
miracle NN I-NP O I-ORG
Stadium NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Wimbledon NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Wimbledon JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Texan NN I-NP I-MISC O
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Washington NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Wimbledon NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
tantrum NN I-NP O I-ORG
All-England NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Club NNP I-NP I-ORG O
lanky JJ I-NP O I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Balls NNS I-NP O I-LOC
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
FOOTBALL-RANDALL NNP I-NP I-MISC O
CUNNINGHAM NNP I-NP I-PER O
PHILADELPHIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cunningham NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Pro FW I-NP I-MISC O
Bowl NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Cunningham NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eagles NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Cunningham NNP I-NP I-PER O
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Eagles NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Lurie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Eagles NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Cunningham NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cunningham NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
GREATER NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Greater NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Milwaukee NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
6,739-yard JJ I-NP O I-PER
Brown NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Deer NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Park NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Golf NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Course NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
62 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Nolan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER O
64 CD I-NP O I-PER
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER O
65 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Billy NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Andrade NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jesper NNP I-NP I-PER O
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER O
66 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Neal NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lancaster NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Barr NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wood NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Claar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russ NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cochran NNP I-NP I-PER O
67 CD I-NP O I-PER
Calcavecchia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Olin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Browne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bortsch NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mike NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hulbert NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Henninger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tiger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jurgenson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bryan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Gorman NNP I-NP I-PER O
HENKE NNP I-NP I-PER O
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
WOODS NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
MAKES NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PRO FW I-NP O I-ORG
DEBUT NN I-NP O I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Nolan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Greater NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Milwaukee NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
20-year-old JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Tiger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Henke NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER O
Andrade NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jesper NNP I-NP I-PER O
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
U.S. NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Amateur NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER O
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Magee NNP I-NP I-PER O
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Texas NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Nortel NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Sometimes RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
champ NN I-NP O I-PER
SILVA NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
'S POS B-NP O I-ORG
`LOST NN I-NP O I-ORG
PASSPORT NN I-NP O I-ORG
' '' I-NP O I-ORG
EXCUSE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NOT RB O O I-ORG
ENOUGH NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Mauro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Silva NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
excused VBN I-VP O I-ORG
DEFEATS NNP I-NP O I-PER
American NNP I-NP I-MISC O
post-Games NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Watched JJ I-ADJP O I-LOC
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Games NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Golden NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Four CD I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
BERLIN NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Berlin NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Bokovec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Djate-Taillard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carmen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wuestenhagen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Margarita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Maruseva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thorsett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Crear NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jarrett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schwarthoff NNP I-NP I-PER O
Falk VBP I-VP I-PER O
Balzer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Busemann NNP I-NP I-PER O
Geir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hirsbro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Astrid NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kumbernuss NNP I-NP I-PER O
Claudia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mues NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Korzhanenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Valentina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fedyushina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Storp NNP I-NP I-PER O
Venuste NNP I-NP I-PER O
Niyongabo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Koers NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vasily NNP I-NP I-PER O
Virgilijus NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alekna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seelig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moellenbeck NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gete NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wami NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cheruiyot NNP I-NP I-PER O
Annemari NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sandell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tegla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Loroupe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gunhild NNP I-NP I-PER O
Halle NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Fabrizio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mori NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nylander NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jearl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yusuf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ruecker NNP I-NP I-PER O
Olabisi NNP B-NP I-PER O
Afolabi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Linda NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kisabaka NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karin NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Janke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Geir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blume NNP O I-PER O
Kipketer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Norberto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tellez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Langat NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nico NNP I-NP I-PER O
Motchebon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kiptoo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hacini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vebjoen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Winrow NNP I-NP I-PER O
1= CD I-NP O I-PER
Tiwontschik NNP I-NP I-PER O
1= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Igor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Trandenkov NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Maksim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tarasov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Igor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Potapovich NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kazakstan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Galfione NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pyotr NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bochkary NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dmitri NNP B-NP I-PER O
Hanne NNP I-NP I-PER O
6= CD I-NP O I-PER
6= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Yelena NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gulyayeva NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Golodnova NNP I-NP I-PER O
El NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hassane NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lahssini NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kororia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brahim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lahlafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bayissa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Conley NNP I-NP I-PER O
Armen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Martirosyan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Calado NNP I-NP I-PER O
Charles-Michael NNP I-NP I-PER O
Friedek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tanja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Damaske NNP I-NP I-PER O
Trine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hattesta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rantanen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiomara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rivero NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shikolen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramaunaskaite NNP I-NP I-PER O
Oeji NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aliu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Falk NN I-NP I-PER O
Balzer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Panayiotopoulos NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Schwarthoff NNP I-NP I-PER O
STANDARD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
LIEGE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
UEFA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Intertoto NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Hellers NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roberto NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bisconti NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Didier NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ernst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bisconti NNP I-NP I-PER O
HARRISON NNP I-NP I-PER O
EDWARDS NNP I-NP I-PER O
MONTE JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CARLO NNS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Olympic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Solidarity NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Meeting NNP I-NP I-MISC O
for IN I-PP I-MISC O
Sarajevo NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kosevo NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Games NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Milan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
IAAF NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Final NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Milan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BARATELLI NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dominique NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baratelli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baratelli NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
and CC O O I-ORG
MILAN NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LENTINI NNP I-NP I-PER O
ATALANTA NNS I-NP I-ORG O
Gianluigi NNP B-NP I-PER O
Lentini NNP I-NP I-PER O
serie VB I-VP I-MISC O
A DT I-NP I-MISC O
Lentini NN I-VP I-PER I-LOC
Bergamo-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
reunites VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Lentini NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ex-Milan JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Fabio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Capello NNP I-NP I-PER O
Emiliano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mondonico NNP I-NP I-PER O
S. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Law NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER O
D. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lehmann NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER O
J. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER O
1-21 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
2-52 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3-97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-149 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5-157 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-163 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
8-198 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9-203 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9-0-49-1 CD I-ADVP O I-LOC
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER O
10-0-38-3 NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Fleming NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fleming NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fleming NNP I-NP I-PER O
U. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chandana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
1-22 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2-78 JJ I-ADVP O I-ORG
3-78 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-78 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5-81 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-196 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Law NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
2-0-23-0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Fleming NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
8-1-26-3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lehmann NNP I-NP I-PER O
6-0-26-0 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Bevan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Man NN I-NP O I-PER
Next JJ I-NP O I-MISC
Series NNP I-NP O I-MISC
elected VBN I-VP O I-LOC
overs NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Damien NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lehmann NNP I-NP I-PER O
Upul JJ I-NP I-PER O
Chandana NNS I-NP I-PER O
ROMANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Romanian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Comelf NN I-NP I-ORG O
Comelf NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Comelf RB I-ADVP I-ORG I-LOC
Transylvanian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Bistrita NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Comelf NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Year-on-year JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Luli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Popescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
POLISH NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
NBP NNP I-NP O I-ORG
REFRAINS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
FROM NNP I-NP O I-ORG
REVERSE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
REPO NNP I-NP O I-ORG
OPERATION NNP I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Poland NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
refrained VBD I-VP O I-LOC
bank NN I-NP O I-LOC
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Canada NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Wk VB I-VP O I-LOC
Notes NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Govt NN I-NP O I-LOC
bills NNS I-NP O I-ORG
152.80 CD B-NP O I-ORG
+0.300 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Chartered NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Canadian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
M1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
63.02 CD I-NP O I-ORG
62.83 CD I-NP O I-ORG
M2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
389.79 CD I-NP O I-ORG
391.32 CD I-NP O I-ORG
M3 NN I-NP O I-ORG
482.13 CD B-NP O I-ORG
480.72 CD I-NP O I-ORG
completes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
ST. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
LOUIS NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
St. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Petersburg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Jones NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Jones NNP I-NP I-ORG O
manufactures VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
prescription NN I-NP O I-ORG
pharmaceutical JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Levoxyl NNP I-NP I-MISC O
NYMEX NN I-NP O I-ORG
heating NN I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NYMEX NN I-NP O I-LOC
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Heat NN I-NP O I-LOC
October NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Buying NN I-NP O I-LOC
NYMEX NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Harry NNP I-NP I-PER O
Milling NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NAPM NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Eurodollar NN I-NP I-MISC O
Eurodollar NN I-NP I-MISC O
Eurodollars NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Rumors NNS I-NP O I-ORG
circulated VBD I-VP O I-ORG
December NNP I-NP O I-LOC
CNBC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Jackson NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Hole NNP I-NP I-MISC O
symposium NN I-NP I-MISC O
FOMC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Eurodollars NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Eurodollars NNP I-NP I-MISC O
FARMINGTON NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
HILLS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
1996-08-30 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Shares NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Magna NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Markham NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ontario-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
's POS I-NP O I-ORG
North JJ I-ADJP I-MISC I-ORG
American JJ I-ADJP I-MISC I-ORG
and CC O O I-ORG
Family-controlled JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Hoey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hoey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Magna NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ford NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Casesa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Magna NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Magna NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
interior NN I-NP O I-ORG
components NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Magna NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Johnson NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Controls NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lear NNP I-NP I-ORG O
UK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
meals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
feeds VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
follow VB I-VP O I-ORG
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
UK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
meals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Ballantyne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Iraqi JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Seven CD I-NP O I-MISC
Amman-bound JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Late JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Bunds NNP I-NP O I-MISC
LIFFE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Chicago NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
PMI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
LIFFE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
LIFFE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
UNITED NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
STATES NNS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Prices NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Labour NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Day NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Trade NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Japanese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Goverment NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Bonds NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-PER
LIFFE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
EUROBONDS NNS I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
DNIB NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
DNIB NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Boxing-Bruno NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
quits VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
WBC NNP O I-ORG O
Tyson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Professor NNP I-NP O I-PER
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Oliver NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McCall NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Tyson NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McCarthy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Irish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Mick NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McCarthy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Birmingham NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Keith NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
O'Neill NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
joins VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Niall NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Quinn NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Breen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Staunton NNP I-NP I-PER O
McAteer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Harte NNP I-NP I-PER O
McLoughlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Houghton NNP I-NP I-PER O
Townsend NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nigerian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Little NNP I-NP O I-PER
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Nigeria NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Uyo NNP I-NP I-LOC O
miners NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Workers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
managers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Nagoum NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yamassoum NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paramilitary JJ I-NP O I-LOC
End-of-year JJ I-NP O I-ORG
examinations NNS I-NP O I-ORG
endorses NNS I-NP O I-PER
Russian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Nikolayevich NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russian NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Federation NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Russian NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Federation NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Chechen NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Tens NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Ruling NNP I-NP O I-MISC
reassured VBN I-VP O I-ORG
Alija NNP I-NP I-PER O
Izetbegovic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Absentee VBN I-VP O I-LOC
Election NN I-NP O I-LOC
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
Europe NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
prohibit VBP I-VP O I-ORG
Aerodrom NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Beograd NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Batajnica NNP I-NP I-LOC O
quotes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Belgrade NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ljubomir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Acimovic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Surcin NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Batajnica NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Acimovic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Batajnica NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Branko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bilbija NNP I-NP I-PER O
Amra NN I-NP I-PER O
Kevic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Top JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Sayenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Semyon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sharetsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sharetsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Sharetsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Posukhov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Sharetsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lukashenko NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Zenon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Poznyak NNP I-NP I-PER O
Naumchik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tajik NN I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kushko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tajik NN I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Tavildara NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Islamic NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Pamir NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Nikolai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sherbatov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tavildara NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Sherbatov NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Tavildara NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Layron NN I-NP I-LOC O
Dushanbe NN I-NP I-LOC O
Shells NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Islamic NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Tens NNS I-NP O I-LOC
shaky JJ I-NP O I-ORG
United NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Nations-sponsored JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Fruit NN I-NP O I-LOC
Rajab NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adinayev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tajik NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Polish NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Poland NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Foreign NNP I-NP O I-ORG
During IN I-PP O I-PER
Federal NNP I-NP I-LOC O
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
Poles NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Poland NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
revived VBD I-VP O I-ORG
punish VB I-VP O I-ORG
Belgrade NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Russian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Earlier RBR I-NP O I-MISC
Yastrzhembsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Barvikha NN I-NP I-LOC O
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Neither DT I-NP O I-PER
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Lavrentyeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Valery NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ivankov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ivankov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lavrentyeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Levrentyeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
France-registered JJ I-NP I-MISC O
BSE NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Frater NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vienna NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Frater NNP I-NP I-PER O
Obviously RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Frater NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Frater NNP I-NP I-PER O
GDRs NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Frater NNP I-NP I-PER O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Laszlo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sebesvari NNP I-NP I-PER O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Kecskemet NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Petofi NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Frater NNP I-NP I-PER O
Romania NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
cen NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Romania NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BNR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
BNR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Potent JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
landmines NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Police NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ornate JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Casa NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
de NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Narino NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Assault NN I-NP O I-LOC
Surinamese-born NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Cambodian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Norodom NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sihanouk NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Vipheak NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sereipheap NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Thmei NNP I-NP I-ORG O
New NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Liberty NNP I-NP I-ORG O
T3 JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Sihanouk NNP I-NP I-PER O
steering NN I-NP O I-ORG
Hen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vipheak NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sihanouk NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Hen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vipheak NNP I-NP I-PER O
KNP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Rattana NNP I-NP I-PER O
Co-Premiers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Prince NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Norodom NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ranariddh NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mishi NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Saran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Southeast NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Singapore NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
premiums NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Indonesian-origin NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Koreans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Continued JJ I-NP O I-ORG
dishoarding NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
kilo-bars NN I-NP O I-ORG
Gold NN I-NP O I-PER
Easier JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Tripoli NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
decks NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Mona NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Eltahawy NNS I-NP I-PER O
Libyans NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Muammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Green NNP I-NP O I-ORG
flags NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Pan NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Am NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lockerbie NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Huge JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Green NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Square NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Niger NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ghana NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Idris NNP I-NP I-PER O
Samer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soliman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Libyans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Tripoli-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jebel NNP I-NP I-LOC O
al-Akhdar NN I-NP I-LOC O
Travellers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Benghazi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Twilight NN I-NP O I-LOC
Belec NNP I-NP I-PER O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Hugh NNP I-NP I-PER O
claims VBZ I-VP O I-PER
Geraghty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Democrat NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Walter NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mondale NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Geraghty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Geraghty NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Whitewater NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Clintons NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Geraghty UH I-INTJ I-PER O
Geraghty UH I-INTJ I-PER O
Brisk JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Somerville NNP I-NP I-PER O
Factory NN I-NP O I-LOC
policy-makers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Lynn NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Reaser NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Banks NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Jacksonville NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Fla NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Incomes NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Economist NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Joel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Naroff NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
FOMC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Naroff NNP I-NP I-PER O
FOMC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
24 CD I-NP O I-LOC
CNBC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Governor NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Lawrence NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lindsey NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lindsey NNP I-NP I-PER O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Michigan NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Reaser NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
considers VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
New JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Orders NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Orders NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Drazek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Drazek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Northern NNP I-NP O I-ORG
California NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
growers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
harmful JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
insects NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Proponents NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Michoacan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Bellamore NNP I-NP I-PER O
California NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
avocado JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Administration NN I-NP O I-LOC
Drazek NNP I-NP I-PER O
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cardinal NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cardinal NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Joseph NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pancreatic JJ I-NP O I-ORG
cancer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Surgeons NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
archdiocese NN I-NP O I-ORG
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bernardin NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
steadfastly RB I-ADVP O I-ORG
Bernardin NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
prayed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Bernardin NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
archbishop NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Cincinnati NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Previously RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
's POS B-NP I-ORG O
Dorfman NNP I-NP I-PER O
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS B-NP I-ORG O
NationsBank NN I-NP I-ORG O
Ancell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Edward NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
D. NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Jones NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Whoever WP I-NP O I-LOC
grab VB I-VP O I-ORG
St. NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Louis-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS I-NP I-ORG O
Kansas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
City NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mo.-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Mercantile NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Roosevelt NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Weber NNP I-NP I-PER O
asset-St NN I-NP I-MISC O
. . O I-MISC O
Louis NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Mercantile NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Weber NNP I-NP I-PER O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Minneapolis-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
and CC O O I-ORG
Ohio-based JJ I-NP I-MISC O
KeyCorp NNP I-NP I-ORG O
One CD I-NP I-ORG O
Representatives NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Norwest NNP I-NP I-ORG O
One CD I-NP I-ORG O
KeyCorp NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
's POS I-NP I-ORG O
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS I-NP I-ORG O
Weber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Talk NN I-NP O I-LOC
NationsBank NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS B-NP I-ORG O
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS I-NP I-ORG O
Ancell NNP I-NP I-PER O
NationsBank NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Boatmen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS I-NP I-ORG O
NationsBank NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Durante NNP I-NP I-PER O
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
tight-lipped JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
Farrakhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Farrakhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
... : O O I-LOC
Farrakhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Farrakhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Muammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gaddafi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Farrakhan JJ I-NP I-PER O
Nation NNP I-NP I-ORG O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Islam NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Farrakhan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Million NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Man NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
March NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Pan NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Am VBP I-NP I-MISC O
flight NN I-NP I-MISC O
103 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Lockerbie NNP I-NP I-LOC O
imposition NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
European JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Mediterranean NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Tentative JJ I-NP O I-LOC
25 CD I-NP O I-LOC
South NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Carolina NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
on IN I-PP I-ORG O
Presidential JJ I-NP I-ORG O
Debates NNS I-NP I-ORG O
League NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Women NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Voters NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Titanic JJ I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Equipment NN I-NP O I-LOC
RMS NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Titanic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Titanic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Newfoundland NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Erin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Purcell NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Boston-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Titanic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Purcell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bonn NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
appeals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Jewish NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
West NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bank NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
settlements NNS I-NP O I-ORG
surrounding VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Jerusalem NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Arab JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
City NN I-NP O I-LOC
Arab-Israeli JJ I-NP I-MISC O
German-Israeli JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Before IN I-PP O I-PER
Saint-Bernard NNP I-NP I-LOC O
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
pro-Socialist JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Most JJS I-NP O I-PER
Communist-led JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Charles NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
de IN I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Gaulle NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER O
Francois NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cabrera NNP I-NP I-PER O
Twenty-three NNP I-NP O I-LOC
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Nichterwitz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Velten NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Public JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Missing JJ I-NP O I-MISC
Dutch JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Nichterwitz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Groningen NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Groningen NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Velten NNP I-NP I-LOC O
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Public JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Descriptions NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Ready JJ I-ADJP O I-LOC
Aluminium NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MARTELA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
taxes NNS I-NP O I-ORG
6.3 CD B-NP O I-ORG
Canadian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
TORONTO TO I-VP I-LOC I-ORG
Canadian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Webber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Statistics NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Canada NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Webber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Traders NNS I-NP I-ORG O
' POS B-NP I-ORG O
Labour NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Day NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Aw NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Revs NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Avg VBG I-VP O I-ORG
shrs NNS I-NP O I-ORG
4,841 CD B-NP O I-ORG
Revs NNS I-NP O I-ORG
476 CD B-NP O I-ORG
Avg VBG I-VP O I-ORG
shrs NNS I-NP O I-ORG
4,666 CD I-NP O I-ORG
All DT I-NP O I-ORG
Data NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Above IN I-PP O I-ORG
000s NNPS I-NP O I-ORG
Except IN I-PP O I-ORG
Per IN I-NP O I-ORG
IPO NN I-NP O I-ORG
Company NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Name NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Nasdaq NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Stock NNP I-NP O I-ORG
ipo VBG I-VP O I-ORG
N NN I-NP O I-ORG
Lead JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Underwriter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Underwriters NNS I-NP O I-ORG
over-allotment NN I-NP O I-ORG
N NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Financial NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Data NNP I-NP O I-ORG
slams NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Arab JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Palestinian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Palestinians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Arab JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Arab JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
occupied JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Arab JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
al-Gama'a NN I-NP I-ORG O
al-Islamiya NN I-NP I-ORG O
Sharqiyah NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Rami NNP I-NP I-PER O
al-Saadani JJ I-ADJP I-PER O
Al-Akhbar JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
State NN I-NP O I-ORG
Gama'a NNP I-NP I-MISC O
purist NN I-NP O I-ORG
Islamic JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Israel NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
blocks NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Palestinian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
pilgrims NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Sami NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Aboudi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kamil NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jamil NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
al-Aqsa JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Jamil NN I-NP I-PER O
Hebrew NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Palestinian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Pilgrims NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Palestinians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
wants VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Arab NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
East NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Jerusalem NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
al-Aqsa NN I-NP I-LOC O
al-Aqsa NN I-NP I-LOC O
Jamil NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
al-Ram JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Khaled NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hijazi NNP I-NP I-PER O
asked VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Mustafa NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hoshiyeh NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
West NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bank NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
labourer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Qalandia NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Time NNP I-NP O I-MISC
ST NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MI NNS I-NP I-LOC O
DUE JJ I-ADJP O I-LOC
PAYING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Bodman NNP I-NP I-ORG O
, , O I-ORG O
1997 CD I-NP O I-LOC
2005 CD I-NP O I-LOC
2006 CD I-NP O I-LOC
2007 CD I-NP O I-LOC
2008 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Somerville NNP I-NP I-PER O
Spending NN I-NP O I-LOC
Incomes NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Department NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Wages NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Orders NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Commerce NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Spending NN I-NP O I-LOC
Payrolls NNS I-NP O I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
5647.65 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Nikkei NNP I-NP I-MISC O
20202.87 CD I-NP O I-LOC
FTSE JJ I-NP I-MISC O
3885.0 CD I-NP O I-LOC
----- JJ I-NP O I-LOC
STOCKS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
SINK NNP I-VP O I-ORG
AS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Blue-chip JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Ralph NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bloch NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shulman NNP I-NP I-PER O
. . O I-ORG O
chief JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Fears NNS I-NP O I-LOC
tightening NN I-NP O I-ORG
Dick NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Morris NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
December NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Overseas RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
100 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Italian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong-based JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Wuxi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Wuxi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
fast-growing JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Far NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Eastern NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Paula NNP B-NP I-PER O
Buratti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Indosuez NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Milan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Unicom NN I-NP I-ORG O
Pirelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SpA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Tonchetti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Provera NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong-listed JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Dutch JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Market-making VBG I-VP O I-LOC
FTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lex NNP I-NP I-PER O
van NNP I-NP I-PER O
Drooge NNP I-NP I-PER O
FTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Flavio NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cotti NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
Europe NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Vienna-based JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Our PRP$ I-NP O I-LOC
Pro-Moscow JJ I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Chechnya NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Zelimkhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yandarbiyev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Cotti NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
principles NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Cotti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dutch JJ I-NP I-MISC O
reopen VB I-VP O I-ORG
carqo VBD I-VP O I-ORG
enquiry RB I-ADVP O I-ORG
THE DT I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
HAGUE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Annemarie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jorritsma NNP I-NP I-PER O
freighter NN I-NP O I-ORG
Tel NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Aviv NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Jorritsma NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Armenians NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Azeris NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Representatives NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Nagorno-Karabakh NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Azerbaijani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vafa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gulizade NNP I-NP I-PER O
Armenian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Zhirayr NNP I-NP I-PER O
Liparityan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nagorno-Karabakh NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Azeri NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Armenians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Azeris NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Nagorno-Karabakh NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Nagorno-Karabakh NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Russia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
Europe NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Minsk NNP I-VP I-ORG O
Group NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Sombre JJ I-NP O I-ORG
mood NN I-NP O I-ORG
Soderlind NNP I-NP I-PER O
Disaster NN I-NP O I-LOC
Stig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Onarheim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Longyear NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Think VB I-VP O I-LOC
Onarheim NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ukrainians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Pyramiden NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Sletten NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sletten VBN I-VP I-PER I-LOC
Teenage NN I-NP O I-ORG
shop NN I-NP O I-ORG
assistant NN I-NP O I-ORG
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Groenstein NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Longyear NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Around IN I-PP O I-MISC
100 CD I-NP O I-MISC
Ukrainian NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
miners NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Longyear NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Longyear NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Everything NN I-NP O I-LOC
Winter NN I-NP O I-PER
Spitzbergen NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
lies VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Inhabited VBN I-VP O I-LOC
Ericsson NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Swedish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Guangdong NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ericsson NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
GPTA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
AXE NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Intelligent NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Network NNP I-NP I-MISC O
IN IN I-PP I-MISC O
Ericsson NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Per IN I-NP I-PER O
Zetterquist NNP I-NP I-PER O
Deliveries NNS I-NP O I-LOC
coast NN I-NP O I-LOC
Auckland NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Telephone NN I-NP O I-LOC
Fax NN I-NP O I-LOC
KOMPAS NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Indonesian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Wahono NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Philippines NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Philippine JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MNLF NNP I-NP I-ORG O
MEDIA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
INDONESIA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Kia NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Motor NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Tanjung NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Priok NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kia NNP I-NP I-ORG O
REPUBLIKA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Net JJ I-NP O I-ORG
415 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Net JJ I-NP O I-ORG
650 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bootleg VBG I-NP O I-ORG
brew NN I-NP O I-ORG
Huize NN I-NP I-LOC O
Yunnan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Post-mortem JJ I-NP O I-ORG
examinations NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Singapore NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
hangs VBZ I-VP O I-MISC
Changi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Prison NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Jeerasak NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Densakul NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nablus JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Palestinian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
West NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bank NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
self-rule JJ I-NP O I-ORG
enclave NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Nablus NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Nablus NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Palestinians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Responding VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Palestinian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
observer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Tono NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eitel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Peleg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eitel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jilani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Holy NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
City NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-LOC I-ORG
Jerusalem NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Burj NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
al-Laqlaq JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Society NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
REAL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
LA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CORUNA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
blushes NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Fabio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Capello NNP I-NP I-PER O
Deportivo NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
playmaker NN I-NP O I-ORG
Corentine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Martins NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brazilian-born NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Spanish NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Donato NNP I-NP I-PER O
Real JJ I-NP I-ORG O
Milla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Armando NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alvarez NNP I-NP I-PER O
despairing JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Songo'o NNP I-NP I-PER O
Donato NNP I-NP I-PER O
incursion NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Augusto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lendoiro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mauro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Toshack NNP I-NP I-PER O
WIGAN NNP I-NP I-ORG O
BRADFORD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ISRAEL NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Haim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hajaj NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sivilia NNP I-NP I-PER O
IRISH JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
ERASE NN I-NP O I-ORG
PAINFUL JJ I-NP O I-ORG
MEMORIES NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
Alpine NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mick NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McCarthy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
20-year-old JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Eschen JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Jack NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Charlton NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
IRELAND NNP I-NP I-LOC O
LIECHTENSTEIN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
284 CD I-NP O I-PER
Allenby JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
285 CD I-NP O I-PER
288 CD I-NP O I-PER
289 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Joakim NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Haeggman NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
290 CD I-NP O I-PER
291 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Phillip NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Price NNP I-NP I-PER O
SLOVAKIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
FAROES NNS I-NP I-LOC O
Mueller NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lubomir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moravcik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dubovsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
the DT I-NP O I-ORG
205-km CD I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
the DT I-NP I-MISC O
Netherlands NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
between IN I-PP O I-ORG
Roermond NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Landgraaf NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Jesper NNP I-NP I-PER O
Skibby NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pavanello NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aki NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Eleuterio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Anguita NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Skibby NNP I-NP I-PER O
BIRMINGHAM NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
1-103 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2-105 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3-163 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-168 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5-221 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-257 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
7-257 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8-286 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Ata-ur-Rehman NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
6-0-40-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
10-0-33-2 CD I-ADVP O I-LOC
pakistan SYM O O I-LOC
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER O
3-54 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
4-104 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5-137 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-164 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
7-164 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9-177 NN I-ADVP O I-LOC
7-0-32-0 NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER O
track NN I-NP O I-LOC
Antonella NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bellutti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marion NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Clignet NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lucy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tyler-Sharman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yvonne NNP I-NP I-PER O
McGregor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karimova NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rasa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mazeikyte NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tatian NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stiajkina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Capelli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cristiano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Citto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mauro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Trentino NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chantyr NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nikolai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kouznetsov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cyril NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Philippe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ermenault NNP I-NP I-PER O
Guido NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fulst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Danilo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hondo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thorsten NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rund NNP I-NP I-PER O
Michelle NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ferris NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Slioussareva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Donna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wynd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mira NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kasslin NNP I-NP I-PER O
11. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Wendy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Everson NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Giovanna NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Troldi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Razmaite NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Capelli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cristiano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Citto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mauro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Trentino NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cyril NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Philippe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ermenault NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arrue NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roberto NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chiappa NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
quarter-finals NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Marion NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Clignet NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
World NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Natalia NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Karimova NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Yvonne NNP I-NP I-PER O
McGregor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lucy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tyler-Sharman NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Samokhvalova NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Antonella NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bellutti NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rasa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mazeikyte NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
all-rounder NN I-NP O I-ORG
Adam NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hollioake NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
GONZALEZ NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
HOMERS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TWICE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
AS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Juan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chad NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Ogea NNP I-NP I-PER O
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Mickey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rivers NNS I-NP I-PER O
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
121 CD I-NP O I-ORG
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
broke VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Ruben NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sierra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Indians NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Oates NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pavlik NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
League NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Central NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Texas NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Tino NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pettitte NNP I-NP I-PER O
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Darryl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Strawberry NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leyritz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pettite JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Mariano NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rivera NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ex-Yankee NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Randy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Velarde NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Seattle NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Incaviglia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Incaviglia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baltimore NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Toronto NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Tapani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Harold NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baines NNP I-NP I-PER O
Robin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ventura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baines NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Danny NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tartabull NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
starters NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Oakland NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Telgheder NNP I-NP I-PER O
McGwire NNP I-NP I-PER O
Athetlics NNP I-NP I-ORG O
7-0 NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Telgheder NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Buddy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Groom NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McGwire NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Detroit NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Poppel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clark NNP I-NP I-PER O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Poppel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kansas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
City NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Milwaukee NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Newfield NNP I-NP I-PER O
Parra NNP I-NP I-PER O
Matt NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lawton NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Fetters NNP I-NP I-PER O
KENT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Kettleborough NNP I-NP I-PER O
tipping VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Our PRP$ I-NP O I-ORG
catching VBG I-VP O I-ORG
12. CD I-NP O I-PER
WELSH JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Welsh NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Harlequins NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Gloucester NNP I-NP I-ORG O
27 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Northampton NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Orrell RB I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Bath NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Sale NN I-NP I-ORG O
Wasps NNP I-NP I-ORG O
25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Welsh NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Bridgend NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Llanelli NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Dunvant NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Treorchy NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Newbridge NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newport NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Caerphilly NNP I-NP I-ORG O
49 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Scottish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Boroughmuir NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hawick NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Currie NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Heriot NN I-NP I-ORG O
's POS B-NP I-ORG O
F.P. NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Jed-Forest JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Watsonians NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
107 CD I-NP O I-ORG
County NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Melville NNP I-NP I-PER O
UKRAINE NNP I-NP I-LOC O
NORTHERN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
IRELAND NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Rebrov NNP I-NP I-PER O
LYNAGH NNP I-NP I-PER O
DWYER NNP I-NP I-ORG O
LEICESTER NN I-NP I-ORG O
Wallaby NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lynagh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dwyer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leicester NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Lynagh NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Saracens NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
millionaire NN I-NP O I-ORG
backer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Nigel NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Wray NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
French JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Philippe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sella NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lynagh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bracken NNP I-NP I-PER O
Harlequins NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Cabannes NNP I-NP I-PER O
Benezech NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gloucester NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bath NN I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Orrell NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Wasps NNS I-NP I-ORG O
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Scottish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
for IN I-PP O I-ORG
Dundee NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Partick NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Stirling NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Livingston NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Ayr NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hamilton NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Dumbarton NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Arbroath NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Montrose VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
LEAGUE NN I-NP O I-MISC
English JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Portsmouth NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Birmingham NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
York NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Preston NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Cardiff NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Northampton NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Lincoln NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Colchester NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Partick NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Stirling NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Ayr NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Dumbarton NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Livingston NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Arbroath NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Montrose VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
LEAGUE NN I-NP O I-MISC
York NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Brentford3 NN I-NP I-ORG O
Colchester NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
CHAMPIONSHIP WDT B-NP I-MISC O
Portsmouth NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Tufnell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chesterfield NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
471 CD B-NP O I-ORG
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
Bicknell NNP I-NP I-PER O
468 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Butcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kersey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ratcliffe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bicknell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leeds NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kettleborough NNP I-NP I-PER O
Such JJ I-NP I-PER O
372 CD B-NP O I-ORG
Hove NNP I-NP I-LOC O
363 CD I-NP O I-ORG
214 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Tolley NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tolley NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bristol NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
190 CD I-NP O I-ORG
INDYCAR NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Sunday NNP I-NP O I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Vancouver NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
IndyCar NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Zanardi NNP I-NP I-PER O
mph NN I-NP O I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
182.778 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Andretti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rahal NNP I-NP I-PER O
Reynard VB I-VP I-ORG O
Mercedes-Benz NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bryan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Herta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Reynard VB I-VP I-ORG O
Mercedes-Benz NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Vasser NNP I-NP I-PER O
Penske NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mercedes-Benz NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Jr NNP I-NP O I-PER
Penske NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mercedes-Benz NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mauricio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gugelmin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gil NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
de NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ferran NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
CANADA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
PANAMA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CONCACAF NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Aunger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Peschisolido NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carlo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Corrazin NNP I-NP I-PER O
FINALLY NN I-NP O I-ORG
BREAK VBD I-VP O I-ORG
SPELL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Colquhoun NNP I-NP I-PER O
ecstatic JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Ellis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Park NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
All DT I-NP I-ORG O
Black NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
South JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
African JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Springbok NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Venter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fullback NNP I-NP O I-PER
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
salvaged VBN I-VP O I-ORG
Recalled VBN I-NP O I-ORG
fly-half NN I-NP O I-ORG
Henry NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Honiball NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Welsh NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
referee NN I-NP O I-PER
Honiball DT I-NP I-PER I-ORG
converted JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
All NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Black NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
hooker NN I-NP O I-PER
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
All DT I-NP I-ORG O
Black NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Venter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Swart NNP I-NP I-PER O
Honiball NNP I-NP I-PER O
Venter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fyvie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kruge NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heerden NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kobus NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiese NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marius NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hurter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dalton NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dawie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Theron NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pagel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alama NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ieremia NNP I-NP I-PER O
ALL MD I-VP I-ORG O
BLACKS NNS I-NP I-ORG O
Ellis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Park NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Joubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Honiball NNP I-NP I-PER O
Honiball NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joubert JJ I-ADJP I-PER O
MAURITANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
NATIONAL NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Lemine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cheiguer NNP I-NP I-PER O
North NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Africans NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MAURITANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
BENIN VB I-VP I-LOC O
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
L NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
L NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
B NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
B NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
N NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
N NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
B NNP I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
) ) O I-ORG O
INCE NNP I-NP I-PER O
GASCOIGNE NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ince NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ince NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Chisinau NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Gascoigne NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
TROFEJ NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BEOGRAD NNP I-NP I-MISC O
TOURNAMENT NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Trofej NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Fifth NN I-NP O I-LOC
92 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Alba NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BASKETBALLSOCCER NNP I-NP O I-LOC
TROFEJ NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BEOGRAD NNP I-NP I-MISC O
TOURNAMENT NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Trofej NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Fifth NN I-NP O I-LOC
92 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Alba NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LITHUANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Viorel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moldovan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Petrescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Constantin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Galca NNP I-NP I-PER O
ARMENIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
PORTUGAL JJ I-NP I-LOC O
AZERBAIJAN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
SWITZERLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Vidadi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rzayev NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
BENETTON NNP I-NP I-ORG O
92-81 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Trofej NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Beograd NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
LATVIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Persson NNP I-NP I-PER O
BELARUS NNP I-NP I-LOC O
ESTONIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Makovsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
MOLDOVA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bruce NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dyer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eadie NNP I-NP I-PER O
HILL MD I-VP I-PER O
JANSHER NNP I-NP I-PER O
Controversial NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hill NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Jansher RB I-ADVP I-PER I-LOC
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jansher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Semifinal JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Hong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Kong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
PARNEVIK NNP I-NP I-PER O
GREATER NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Jesper NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Greater NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Milwaukee NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Parnevik NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Brown NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Deer NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Park NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Golf NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Course NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kraft NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nolan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
1993 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Tiger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Woods NNPS I-NP I-PER O
U.S. NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Amateur NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Parnevik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Whenever WRB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Henke NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Henke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jasper NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bob NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Appleby NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kraft NNP I-NP I-PER O
SPAIN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
OPEN IN I-PP O I-MISC
1997 CD I-NP I-MISC O
FED NNP I-NP I-MISC O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Fed NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Spain NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
travels VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Life NN I-NP O I-LOC
Billie NNP B-NP I-PER O
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
Salzburg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Nagoya NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Fed NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fed NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
King NNP I-NP I-PER O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Petra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Langrova NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
1997 CD I-NP I-MISC O
FED NNP I-NP I-MISC O
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
TEAM NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TOURNAMENT NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Draw VB I-VP O I-LOC
1997 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Fed NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
II NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Slovak VBD I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
EL NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
SALVADOR NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
LOS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
ANGELES NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Joe-Max NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wynalda NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lazo NNP I-NP I-PER O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
DETROIT NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
SEATTLE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
TORONTO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MILWAUKEE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
TEXAS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
OAKLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CALIFORNIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
84 CD I-NP O I-ORG
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
PITTSBURGH NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CINCINNATI NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
PHILADELPHIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MONTREAL NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kansas NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
City NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Chicago NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Baltimore NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Florida NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Houston NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Colorado NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
KEVIN NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
BROWN NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
LOWERS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
ERA NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
AS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
REDS NNS I-NP I-ORG O
CINCINNATI NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
National NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
League NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Bolesy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nolan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ryan NNP I-NP I-PER O
( ( O I-PER O
) ) O I-PER O
Seaver NNP I-NP I-PER O
( ( I-LST I-PER O
Jerry NNP I-NP I-PER I-MISC
) ) O I-PER O
Koosman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Delino VBG I-VP I-PER O
DeShields NNP I-NP I-PER O
Parrett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Darren NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dreifort NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Todd NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Worrell NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Los NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Angeles NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Ryne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sandberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Atlanta NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Glavine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chipper NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cubs NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hernandez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mike NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mordecai NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Montreal NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Sanders NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sanders NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Mike NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Oquist NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Montreal NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Marvin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Benard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shawn NNP I-NP I-PER O
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER O
Benard RB I-ADVP I-PER I-LOC
Harnisch NNP I-NP I-PER O
Estes NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Rod NNP I-NP I-PER O
Beck NNP I-NP I-PER O
Beck JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Alvaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Espinoza NNP I-NP I-PER O
RBI NNS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Brent NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mayne NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
St NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Pagnozzi NNP I-NP I-PER O
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
defeated VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Ray NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lankford NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pittsburgh NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
RBI NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Wall NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Refusing VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Karbacher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karbacher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lendl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karbacher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karbacher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wimbledon NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
countryman NN I-NP O I-PER
Like IN I-PP O I-LOC
BOXING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
PRINCE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NASEEM NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
RETAINS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
WBO IN I-PP O I-ORG
FEATHERWEIGHT NN I-NP O I-ORG
Britain NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Naseem NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hamed NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
retained VBD I-VP O I-ORG
WBO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Manuel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Medina NNP I-NP I-PER O
DOMINATE NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Pagani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stephan JJ I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Marasek NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Schopp NNP I-NP I-PER O
Konsel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heraf NNP I-NP I-PER O
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Dietmar NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kuehbauer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Austrian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Prohaska NNP I-NP I-PER O
Konsel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schopp NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schoettel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pfeffer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Feiersinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stephan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marasek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramusch NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ogris NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dietmar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kuehbauer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Herfried NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sabitzer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Herzog NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heraf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goram NNP I-NP I-PER O
Burley NNP I-NP I-PER O
Boyd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Calderwood NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hendry NNP I-NP I-PER O
McKinley NNP I-NP I-PER O
McCall NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gordon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Durie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
BOXING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
American NNP I-NP I-MISC O
IBF NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Euro NNP I-NP I-MISC O
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Ouedec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Youri NNP I-NP I-PER O
Djorkaeff NNP I-NP I-PER O
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
sending-off NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Franck NNP B-NP I-PER O
Leboeuf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leboeuf NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
fouling NN I-NP O I-ORG
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
substitute NN I-NP O I-ORG
Ricardo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pelaez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mexicans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Zinedine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zidane NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Djorkaeff PRP I-NP I-PER O
Ouedec NNP I-NP I-PER O
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Joaquin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
del FW I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Olmo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Within IN I-PP O I-LOC
Ouedec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Djorkaeff NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jacquet NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Lilian NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thuram NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sabri NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lamouchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER O
Franck NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leboeuf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bixente NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lizarazu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karembeu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Didier NNP I-NP I-PER O
Deschamps NNP I-NP I-PER O
Youri NNP I-NP I-PER O
Djorkaeff NNP I-NP I-PER O
Reynald NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pedros NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ouedec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Maurice NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zinedine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zidane NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alfonso NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pardo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Duilio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Davino NNP I-NP I-PER O
Becerril NNP I-NP I-PER O
German JJ I-NP I-PER I-MISC
Joaquin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
del FW I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Olmo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cuauhtemoc NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blanco NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aspe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramirez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arellano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Enrique NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Palencia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ricardo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pelaez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ouedec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Youri NNP I-NP I-PER O
Djorkaeff NNP I-NP I-PER O
BELGIUM NNP I-NP I-LOC O
TURKEY NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
DESPITE IN I-PP O I-ORG
CROWD NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TROUBLE NN I-NP O I-ORG
Bert NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Lauwers NNP I-NP I-PER O
1998 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Turkish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Riot NN I-NP O I-LOC
Sergen NNP B-NP I-PER O
Yalcin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yalcin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Elleray NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marc NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Degryse NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Medved NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brazilian-born JJ I-ADJP O I-PER
Rustu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Recber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ogun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Temizkanoglu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Wilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arif NNP I-NP I-PER O
Erdem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Orhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cikirikci NNP I-NP I-PER O
Degryse JJ I-NP I-PER O
Recber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bertrand NNP I-NP I-PER O
Crasson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Medved NNP I-NP I-PER O
Renier NNP I-NP I-PER O
Geoffrey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Claeys NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gunther NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schepens NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Nico NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kerckhoven NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Verheyen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Peiremans NNP I-NP I-PER O
Degryse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gilles NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rustu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Recber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hakan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Unsal NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sergen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yalcin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Recep NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cetin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ogun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Temizkanoglu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alpay NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ozalan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ercan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tolunay NNP B-NP I-PER O
Kafkas NNP I-NP I-PER O
Oguz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cetin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arif NNP I-NP I-PER O
Erdem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tayfun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Korkut NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hakan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sukur NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saffet NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sancakli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Orhan NNP B-NP I-PER O
Cikirikci NNP I-NP I-PER O
Belgian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Moer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Moer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Himst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Moer NNP I-NP I-PER O
SPANISH NNS I-NP I-MISC O
division NN I-NP I-MISC O
Corentine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Martins NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Attendancce NNP I-NP O I-ORG
35,000 CD I-NP O I-ORG
SPANISH JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
division NN I-NP I-MISC O
BELGIUM NNP I-NP I-LOC O
TURKEY NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Degryse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sergen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yalcin NNP I-NP I-PER O
BOXING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
KNOCK-OUT NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SPECIALIST NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MILLER NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
DEFENDS VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Nate NNP I-NP I-PER O
WBA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Heath NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
Marcello NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goncalves NNPS I-NP I-PER O
BOXING VBG I-VP O I-LOC
MILLER NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
DEFENDS VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
CRUISERWEIGHT NNP I-NP O I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Nate NNP I-NP I-PER O
WBA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
TATTERSALLS NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BREEDERS NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Tattersalls NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Breeders NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Stakes NNS I-NP I-MISC O
The DT I-NP I-LOC O
Curragh NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Miss NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Stamper NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Paddy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lad NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bloomfield NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pelham NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warren NNP I-NP I-PER O
O'Connor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Distances NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Beryll NNP I-NP I-PER O
Remblance NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hannon NNP I-NP I-PER O
KLINSMANN NNP I-NP I-PER O
1998 CD I-NP I-MISC O
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Sueddeutsche NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Zeitung NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Coach NNP I-NP O I-PER
96 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Luebeck NNP I-NP I-ORG O
LITHUANIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Cosmin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Contra NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mihai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tararache NNP I-NP I-PER O
Danius NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gleveckas NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paper NN I-NP O I-LOC
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Margaret NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
IRA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
The DT I-NP I-ORG O
Sunday NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Telegraph NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Majorie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Libran NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ingram NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ingham NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ingram NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Iron NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lady NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Nancy NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
My PRP$ I-NP I-MISC O
Turn VB I-VP I-MISC O
1533 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Queen NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Elizabeth NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
I PRP B-NP I-PER O
Daughter NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Henry NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
VIII NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boleyn NNP I-NP I-PER O
1706 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Duke NNP I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Orleans NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
besieging VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Turin NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Austrians NNS I-NP I-MISC O
1714 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Treaty NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-MISC I-ORG
Baden NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Roman NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Emperor NNP I-NP O I-PER
VI NNP I-NP I-PER O
Succession NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Charles NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ceded VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Alsace NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Strasbourg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Breisach NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kehl NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Freiburg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
1812 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Kutuzov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Napoleon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Borodino NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Napoleon NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
1822 CD I-NP O I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-PER O
1836 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Campbell-Bannerman NNP I-NP I-PER O
As IN I-SBAR O I-ORG
Liberal NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Transvaal NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Trades NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Disputes NNP I-NP I-MISC O
1860 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Giuseppe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Garibaldi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Red NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Shirts NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Naples NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Austrians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
1901 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Boxer NN I-NP I-MISC O
Rising VBG I-NP I-MISC O
Peking NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Protocol NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Boxer NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Elia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kazan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Elia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kazanjoglus NNP I-NP I-PER O
Viva FW I-VP I-MISC O
Zapata NNP I-NP I-MISC O
On IN I-PP I-MISC O
the DT I-NP I-MISC O
Waterfront VBG I-NP I-MISC O
1913 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Quayle NNP I-NP I-PER O
British JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Best JJS I-NP O I-ORG
Ice NN I-NP I-MISC O
Cold NNP I-NP I-MISC O
in IN I-PP I-MISC O
Alex NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Lawrence NNP I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
Arabia NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Wolsey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Anne NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
a DT I-NP I-MISC O
Thousand NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Days NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
1914 CD I-NP O I-LOC
1930 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Baudouin NNP B-NP I-PER O
I PRP I-NP I-PER O
1940 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Two CD I-NP I-MISC O
Hermann NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goering NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blitz NNP I-NP I-MISC O
1969 CD I-NP O I-LOC
1986 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Anglicans NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Kuwaiti NNP I-NP I-MISC O
historian NN I-NP O I-PER
Percivale NNP I-NP I-PER O
( ( O I-PER O
A.J.P. NNP I-NP I-PER O
) ) O I-PER O
shaped VBN I-VP O I-ORG
modern JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Europe NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
1993 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Uzbekistan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
1994 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Stars NNP I-NP I-MISC O
and CC I-NP I-MISC O
Stripes NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Escaped VBN I-VP O I-MISC
Trevor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Holland NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Worthing NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Holland NNP I-NP I-PER O
Holland NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Scottish NNP I-NP I-ORG O
narrowly RB I-VP O I-ORG
backs VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
British NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Scots NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Conservatives NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Scottish NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
condemns VBZ I-VP O I-LOC
condemned VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Iraqi JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
involvement NN I-NP O I-ORG
condemn VBP I-VP O I-ORG
Iraqi JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
involvement NN I-NP O I-ORG
Arbil JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
lies NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seven CD I-NP O I-MISC
Seven CD I-NP O I-MISC
Flight NN I-NP I-MISC O
150 CD B-NP I-MISC O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
London-based JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Staouelli NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Islamic JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
fundamentalists NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Baseball-Results NNS I-NP O I-LOC
S. NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
African NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Afrikaners NNPS I-NP B-MISC I-ORG
Northern NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cape NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Afrikaners NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Afrikaner JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Afrikaners NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Northern NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cape NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Afrikaans NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Rwandan JJ I-NP I-MISC O
for IN I-PP I-ORG O
the DT I-NP I-ORG O
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
Rwanda NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Refugees NNS I-NP O I-ORG
appeals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Zairean JJ I-NP I-MISC O
RDR NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Zairean JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Hutu NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
that WDT I-NP O I-LOC
Tuzla NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Moslems NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Fights NNS I-NP O I-LOC
reporter NN I-NP O I-ORG
helicopters NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Chechens NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Crowds NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
pro-independence JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Chechens NNS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
greeted VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Urus-Martan JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Adults NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Dzhokhar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dudayev NNP I-NP I-PER O
. . O O I-LOC
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
mainly-Moslem JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
North NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Caucasus NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mubatik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dagayeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aiza NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dudayeva NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dudayeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Urus-Martan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Moscow-backed JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Doku NNP B-NP I-PER O
Zavgayev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mouldi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mamatuyev NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nurbika NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mamatuyeva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mamatuyev NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Lisa NNP B-NP I-PER O
Akhbar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Freedom NNP I-NP O I-ORG
. . O O I-LOC
Islamic JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Sheriat JJ I-ADJP I-MISC O
Islamic NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Polish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
newsstand NN I-NP O I-ORG
BRE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hachette NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Zycie NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Warszawy NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Multico NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Zygmunt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Solorz NNP I-NP I-PER O
BRE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Warsaw NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
division NN I-NP I-MISC O
Hachette NNP I-NP I-ORG O
UWP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
News-stand NN I-NP O I-ORG
chain NN I-NP O I-ORG
Wieslaw NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kaczmarek NNPS I-NP I-PER O
sum NN I-NP O I-ORG
Initially RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Kaczmarek NNP I-NP I-PER O
UWP-Hachette NN I-NP I-ORG O
SPC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SPC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
UWP-Hachette NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Kaczmarek NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Barker NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sergiyev NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Posad NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Attacks NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Cuban JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Soler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Granma NNP B-NP I-ORG O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bertillon NNP I-NP I-MISC O
166 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Fidel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Castro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER O
pre-Castro JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Fulgencio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Batista NNP I-NP I-PER O
In IN I-PP I-MISC O
the DT I-NP I-MISC O
Year NNP I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
January NNP I-NP I-MISC O
The DT I-NP I-MISC O
Collapse NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Sleeping NN I-NP I-MISC O
Bread NNP I-NP I-MISC O
The DT I-NP I-MISC O
Decaying NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mansion NNP I-NP I-MISC O
A DT I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-MISC O
Things NNS I-NP I-MISC O
The DT I-NP I-MISC O
Knot NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Soul NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Alone RB I-ADVP I-MISC O
A DT I-NP I-MISC O
Woman NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Granma NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Sleeping NN I-NP I-MISC O
Bread NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Prensa NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Latina NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Puig NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
SANTIAGO NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Madeleine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Insulza NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bolivia NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Cochabamba NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Guatemala NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Michoacan JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Michoacan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Tacambaro NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Michoacan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Morelia NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Gonzalo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Montoya NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tacambaro NNP I-NP I-LOC O
AK-47s NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Montoya NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
self-styled JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Donghai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiao NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Qiang NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Strike NN I-NP I-MISC O
Hard NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Deng NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiaoping NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiao NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiao FW I-INTJ I-PER O
Xiao NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Hangzhou NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Xiao NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Longde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xiao NNP I-NP I-PER O
hails VBZ I-VP O I-LOC
Fidel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Philippine JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mindanao NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aung NNP I-NP I-PER O
San NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Most JJS I-NP O I-PER
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Win NNP I-NP I-PER O
Htein NNP I-NP I-PER O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SLORC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Most RBS I-NP O I-PER
Insein NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Prison NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hla NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Than IN I-PP I-PER I-ORG
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Insein NNP I-NP I-LOC O
( ( O I-PER O
Leo NNP O I-PER O
) ) O I-PER O
Nichols NNP I-NP I-PER O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Insein NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
NLD NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Dow NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Chemical NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Dow NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Chemical NNP I-NP I-ORG O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Daily NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Tianjin JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
boasts VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Multinational JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Mobil NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
urges VBZ I-VP O I-LOC
South JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
In-so NNP I-NP I-PER O
Song-ho NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kang NNP I-NP I-PER O
Young-hoon NNP I-NP I-PER O
South JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Korean JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
unification NN I-NP O I-ORG
ministry NN I-NP O I-ORG
War NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Yonhap JJ I-NP I-ORG O
North NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
War NNP I-NP O I-MISC
unconditionally RB I-ADVP O I-ORG
repatriated VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Li NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
In-mo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
South NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Chinese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Chinese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Donghai NNP I-NP I-PER O
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hangzhou NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Zhejiang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
1966-76 CD I-ADVP I-MISC O
Hangzhou NNP I-NP I-LOC O
1979 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Re-education JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Tiananmen NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Chinese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Western JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
detains NNS I-NP O I-ORG
dissident NN I-NP O I-ORG
Wang NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Donghai NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chinese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Donghai NNP I-NP I-PER O
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
1979 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Re-education JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Tiananmen NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Chun-yeh NNP I-NP I-PER O
High NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Tell VB I-VP O I-LOC
Nationalist JJ I-NP O I-MISC
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Daily NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Wuhan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Hubei NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Wuhan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
consumes NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Guangzhou NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Guangdong NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Iranian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Chuman NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Faik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nerweyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nerweyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Nerweyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
collaborating VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Northern NNP I-NP O I-LOC
U.S.-led JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Ceasefire JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Islamic JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Representatives NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Naqoura NNP I-NP I-LOC O
in IN I-PP I-ORG O
Lebanon NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
UNIFIL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Sikhin JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Around IN I-PP O I-MISC
1,000 CD I-NP O I-MISC
Hizbollah NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
KPD NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
aid-U.N. NN I-NP I-MISC O
) ) O O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Massoud NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Barzani NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Saladdin NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Fire NNP I-NP O I-ORG
destroys VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Bahraini NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bahraini NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Shul'ala NNP I-NP I-LOC O
al-Daih JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Manama NNP I-NP I-LOC O
from IN I-PP O I-LOC
Barzani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Barzani NNP I-NP I-PER O
flags NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Habib NNP I-NP I-PER O
Boulares NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zine NNP I-NP I-PER O
al-Abidine JJ I-NP I-PER O
Automakers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
DETROIT NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Automakers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Interstate NNP I-NP I-LOC O
95 NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Interstates NNP I-NP I-LOC O
80 CD I-NP I-LOC O
90 CD I-NP I-LOC O
Interstate NNP I-NP I-LOC O
5 CD I-NP I-LOC O
Air NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Bag NNP B-NP O I-ORG
Safety NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Janet NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dewey NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
industry-funded JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Campaign NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Automakers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
petitioned VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Dewey NNP I-NP I-PER O
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Hampshire NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
motel NN I-NP O I-ORG
explodes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
N.H. NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Adds VBZ I-VP O I-LOC
An DT I-NP O I-ORG
explosion NN I-NP O I-ORG
leveled VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Rochester NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
one-story JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Lilac NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Falls NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Motel NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Penney NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rochester NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Fire NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Boston NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Lilac NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Motel NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Car NN I-NP O I-LOC
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
drag NN I-NP O I-ORG
Carl NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Vinson NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Enterprise NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Mediterranean NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Kennett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Troy NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
Tennessee NNP I-NP I-LOC O
F NN I-NP I-MISC O
/ SYM O I-MISC O
A-18 NN I-NP I-MISC O
Vinson NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Enterprise NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
F-15 NN I-NP I-MISC O
F-16 NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Marines NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Most JJS I-NP O I-PER
Marines NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Carl NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Vinson NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Rachel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Severine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Late JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Rachel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Legeard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Severine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Potty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Algerian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Staoueli NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Liberte JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Algerian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
ONDH NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Iranian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Gust NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gust NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Dini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nyerere NNS I-NP I-PER O
Italian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Lamberto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nyerere NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nyerere RB I-ADVP I-PER I-LOC
Wolpe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roman NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Nyerere NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Great NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Lakes NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Nyerere NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Artisans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
for IN I-PP I-MISC O
Nato NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Chatelet NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Chatelineaux NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Fal NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Belgian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Late JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Rachel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Legeard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Severine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Potty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Legeard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nandrin NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Controversial NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Venice NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Vera NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Haller NNP I-NP I-PER O
VENICE NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Dublin-born JJ I-NP O I-ORG
director NN I-NP O I-ORG
Neil NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Michael NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Collins NNP I-NP I-MISC O
IRA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Venice NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Film NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Festival NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Neeson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Irish NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Republican NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Army NNP I-NP I-ORG O
British-ruled JJ I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Warner NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Bros NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Very RB I-NP O I-ORG
rarely RB I-ADVP O I-ORG
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
The DT I-NP I-MISC O
Crying NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Game NNP I-NP I-MISC O
IRA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mao NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tse-Tung NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yitzak NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shamir NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leeson NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Northern NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Ireland-born NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
actor NN I-NP O I-ORG
Schindler NNP I-NP I-MISC O
's POS B-NP I-MISC O
List NN I-NP I-MISC O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Aidan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Quinn NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
portrays VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Harry NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boland NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kitty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kiernan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Much JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Noting VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Collins NNP I-NP I-PER O
Michael NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Collins NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shakil NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rizvi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Broker NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Khurshid NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Alam NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
IDLC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bangladesh NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Lamps NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Atlas NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Bangladesh NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
