JAPAN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CHINA NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nadim NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Ladki NNP I-NP I-PER O
United NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Arab NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Emirates NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Uzbekistan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Uzbek NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Igor JJ B-NP I-PER O
Shkvyrin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Oleg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shatskiku NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Uzbekistan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Takuya NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Takagi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hiroshige NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yanagimoto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Salem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Defender NNP I-NP O I-PER
Bitar NN I-NP I-PER O
Nader NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jokhadar NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bitar NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Shu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kamo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hosts NNPS I-NP O I-LOC
CUTTITTA NNP I-NP I-PER O
ITALY JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Italy NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
recalled VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Marcello NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cuttitta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Murrayfield NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Cuttitta NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Coste NNP I-NP I-PER O
Twickenham NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Stefano NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bordon NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Coste NNP I-NP I-PER O
Corrado NNP B-NP I-PER O
Covi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cuttitta NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
1995 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Coste NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Coste NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pertile NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paolo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vaccari NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marcello NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cuttitta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Francescato NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leandro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Manteri NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dominguez NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mazzariol NNP I-NP I-PER O
Troncon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Orazio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arancio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sgorlon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Massimo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Giovanelli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carlo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Checchinato NNP I-NP I-PER O
Walter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cristofoletto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Properzi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Curti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carlo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Orlandi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Massimo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cuttitta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Giambatista NNP I-NP I-PER O
Croci NNP I-NP I-PER O
Guidi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nicola NNP I-NP I-PER I-MISC
Mazzucato NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moscardi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Castellani NNP I-NP I-PER O
JAPAN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
SYRIA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
United NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Arab NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Emirates NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Takuya NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Takagi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Salem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Defender NNP I-NP O I-PER
Bitar NN I-NP I-PER O
Nader NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jokhadar NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Awad NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kenichi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shimokawa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar NN I-NP I-PER O
Kazuyoshi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Miura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Takagi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Miura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Naoki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kenichi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shimokawa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hiroshige NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yanagimoto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Naoki NNP B-NP I-PER O
Soma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Masami NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ihara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Norio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Omura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Motohiro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yamaguchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Masakiyo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Maezono NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yasuto NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Honda NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Takuya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Takagi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hiroshi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nanami NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kazuyoshi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Miura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hiroaki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Morishima NNP I-NP I-PER O
Masayuki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Okano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Salem NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bitar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bachar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Srour NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tarek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jabban NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Awad NNP I-NP I-PER O
Louay JJ I-NP I-PER O
Taleb NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nihad NNP I-NP I-PER O
al-Boushi NNS I-NP I-PER O
Afash NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dib NNP I-NP I-PER O
Helou NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ammar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rihawiy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Khaled VBD I-VP I-PER O
Zaher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nader NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jokhadar NNP I-NP I-PER O
FREESTYLE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
freestyle JJ I-NP O I-ORG
skiing NN I-NP O I-ORG
moguls NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Jesper NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ronnback NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ivanov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jean-Luc NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brassard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Korneilus NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hole NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jeremie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Collomb-Patton NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dominick NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gauthier NNP I-NP I-PER O
Johann NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gregoire NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tatjana NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mittermayer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Candice NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gilg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Minna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karhu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tae NNP I-NP I-PER O
Satoya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Battellle NNP I-NP I-PER O
Donna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Weinbrecht NNP I-NP I-PER O
Liz NNP I-NP I-PER O
McIntyre NNP I-NP I-PER O
Koroleva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ljudmila NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dymchenko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Katleen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Allais NNPS I-NP I-PER O
ASIAN NNP I-NP I-MISC O
United NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Arab NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Emirates NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Takuya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Takagi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nader NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jokhadar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Uzbekistan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Shkvyrin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Igor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shatskikh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Oleg NNP I-NP I-PER O
for IN I-PP O I-ORG
PAKISTAN NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
V NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NEW JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
ZEALAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
one-day JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Zahoor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Elahi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Spearman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Inzamamul JJ I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Haq NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
st NN I-NP O I-ORG
Germon NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Astle NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shahid NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Afridi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Astle NNP I-NP I-PER O
Germon NNP B-NP I-PER O
2-225 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3-240 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-247 CD I-ADVP O I-ORG
5-252 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-260 CD I-NP O I-ORG
7-261 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8-269 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Doull VB I-NP I-PER O
Cairns NNS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
8-1-35-1 JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
Astle NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
9-0-53-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
B. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Young NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
C. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Spearman NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
A. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Parore NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Saqlain NNP I-NP I-PER O
Afridi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saqlain NNP I-NP I-PER O
N. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Astle NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
L. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Germon NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Afridi NNP I-NP I-PER O
S. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Doull NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
2-7 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
3-125 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-146 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
5-170 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
6-190 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8-213 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9-216 CD I-ADVP O I-ORG
6-0-32-2 RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
10-0-42-0 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Shahid NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Afridi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
7-0-40-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Cup NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BLINKER NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dutch JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Reggie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blinker NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wednesday NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Blinker NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
slapped VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Wednesday NNP I-NP I-ORG O
FIFA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
inform VB I-VP O I-ORG
Blinker NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Engllsh NNP I-NP I-MISC O
' POS B-NP O I-ORG
BOWYER NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
FINED VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Bowyer NNP I-NP I-PER O
McDonald NNP I-NP I-ORG O
's POS B-NP I-ORG O
Bowyer RB I-ADVP I-PER I-LOC
Bowyer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bowyer RB I-ADVP I-PER I-LOC
Yorkshire NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
EUROLEAGUE NNP I-NP I-MISC O
EuroLeague NN I-NP I-MISC O
basketball NN I-NP O I-LOC
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Limoges NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Panionios NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Alba NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Berlin NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Charleroi NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Panathinaikos NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Ljubljana NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Villeurbanne NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Split NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Pau-Orthez NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Sevilla NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LITTLE NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
CAMPESE NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kitson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Barbarians NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Twickenham NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Queenslander NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Owen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Finegan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Manu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wallabies NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Campese NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wallabies NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Campese NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Barbarians NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Campo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Twickenham NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Barbarians NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Stimpson NNP I-NP I-PER O
All DT I-NP I-ORG O
Black NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
forwards RB I-ADVP O I-PER
Hewitt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Barbarians NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Stimpson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bateman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gregor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Townsend NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rob NNP I-NP I-PER O
Howley NNP I-NP I-PER O
Quinnell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Back RB I-ADVP I-PER O
Dale NNP I-NP I-PER O
McIntosh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pontypridd NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Quinnell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Garforth NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leicester NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Hewitt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Popplewell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Burke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roff NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Campese NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brial NNP I-NP I-PER O
Owen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Finegan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Giffin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blades NNP I-NP I-PER O
Caputo NNP I-NP I-PER O
ZIMBABWE NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Zimbabwe NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
par-72 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Chapman NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Golf NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Club NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
South NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
African NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Terblanche NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vuuren NNP I-NP I-PER O
Price NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hobday NNP I-NP I-PER O
Andrew NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pitts NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cayeux NNP I-NP I-PER O
Murless NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hennie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Swart NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schalk NNP I-NP I-PER O
Desvonde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Botes NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Whitelaw NNP I-NP I-PER O
Liddle NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hugh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baiocchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adilson NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
da NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Silva NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Daniels NNP I-NP I-PER O
Trevor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dodds NNP I-NP I-PER O
Robertson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dion NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fourie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Steve NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Waltman NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dougan NNP I-NP I-PER O
MACEDONIA NN I-NP I-LOC O
Romania NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
trainer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Anghel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Iordanescu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Viorel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ion NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Liviu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ciobotariu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Iordanescu NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
title-holders JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Attacking VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Bogdan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stelea NNP I-NP I-PER O
Florin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Prunea NNP I-NP I-PER O
Petrescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Prodan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dobos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cornel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Papura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Liviu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ciobotariu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tibor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Selymess NNP I-NP I-PER O
Iulian NNP I-NP I-PER O
Filipescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gheorghe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hagi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gheorghe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Popescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Constantin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Galca NNP I-NP I-PER O
Basarab NNP I-NP I-PER O
Panduru NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dorinel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Munteanu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ovidiu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stinga NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ioan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vladoiu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gheorghe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Craioveanu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ionel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Danciulescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Viorel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ion NNP I-NP I-PER O
REUTER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LARA NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ENDURES NNP I-NP O I-ORG
ANOTHER NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MISERABLE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
DAY NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Galvin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
All-rounder JJ I-NP O I-PER
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Man-of-the JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lara NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clive NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lloyd NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Melbourne NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Shivnarine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chanderpaul NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chanderpaul NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
AUSTRALIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
V NNP I-NP O I-ORG
WEST NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
INDIES NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
WORLD NN I-NP I-MISC O
SERIES NNS I-NP I-MISC O
limited JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
R. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Samuels NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
S. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chanderpaul NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
N. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McLean NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
1-11 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2-38 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3-64 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
4-73 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5-81 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6-120 CD I-NP O I-ORG
7-135 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9-153 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
10-1-25-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
M. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Taylor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
McLean NNP I-NP I-PER O
McLean NNP I-NP I-PER O
G. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
S. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Law NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
T. NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ambrose NN I-NP I-PER O
Walsh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Benjamin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
9.4-0-43-1 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
McLean NNP I-NP I-PER O
10-1-33-2 CD I-NP O I-LOC
INDIES NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Melbourne NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ground NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Shivnarine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chanderpaul NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
WEST NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
INDIES NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
172 CD I-NP O I-ORG
ALL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
49.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
OVERS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
V NNP I-NP O I-ORG
AUSTRALIA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
SHEFFIELD NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
SHIELD NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Sheffield NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Shield NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Bellerive NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Tasmania NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
352 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Boon NNP I-NP I-PER O
DiVenuto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Victoria NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LARA NNP I-NP I-PER O
AUSTRALIAN IN I-PP O I-MISC
TOUR JJ I-NP O I-MISC
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
medium NN I-NP O I-ORG
pacer NN I-NP O I-ORG
Tom NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Melbourne NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ground NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Clive NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lloyd NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Sydney NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ground NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
INDIES NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Melbourne NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Cricket NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Ground NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Blewett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tom NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Moody NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Warne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gillespie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sherwin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Samuels NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shivnarine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chanderpaul NNP I-NP I-PER O
Junior NNP I-NP I-PER O
McLean NNP I-NP I-PER O
Curtly NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ambrose NNP I-NP I-PER O
Roland NNP I-NP I-PER O
Holder NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dong NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jiong NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Sun NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sidek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Allan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Budi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kuksuma NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Poul-Erik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hoyer-Larsen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Budi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Santoso NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sun NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Budi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kusuma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Audina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Ye NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zhaoying NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Meiluawati NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Susi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Susanti NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Han NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jingna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Susi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Susanti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Camilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ye NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zhaoying NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zichao NNP I-NP I-PER O
ARAB NNP I-NP I-MISC O
National NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
stadium NN I-NP I-LOC O
Sodigraf JJ I-ADJP I-ORG O
Aly RB I-ADVP I-PER I-ORG
Ashour NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ouda NNP I-NP I-PER O
Contractors NNS I-NP O I-LOC
NHL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
League NNP I-NP I-ORG O
NORTHEAST NN I-NP O I-LOC
HARTFORD NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BUFFALO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
OTTAWA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
DALLAS NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
PHOENIX NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
VANCOUVER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
EDMONTON NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
SAN NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
JOSE NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
CALGARY NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ANAHEIM NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ANAHEIM NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BUFFALO NNP I-NP I-LOC O
NY NNP I-NP I-ORG O
RANGERS NNS I-NP I-ORG O
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
COLORADO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
OTTAWA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
EDMONTON NNP I-NP I-LOC O
NHL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NHL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ny NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Islanders NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
) ) O O I-LOC
League NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hartford NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Ny NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Islanders NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Calgary NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Phoenix NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Tampa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Bay NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
AMERICAN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
EAGLES NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Indianapolis NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Colts NNP I-NP I-ORG O
37-10 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Marshall NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Faulk NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Belser NNP I-NP I-PER O
Colts NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Eagles NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Harbaugh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Colts NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Cincinnati NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Eagles NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
East NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Dallas NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Cowboys NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Washington NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Redskins NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Arizona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
idle JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Colts NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Siragusa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Buchanan NNP I-NP I-PER O
linebacker VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Quentin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Coryatt NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Faulk NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Harbaugh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Third-stringer JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Kerwin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bell NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Miami NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Dolphins NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Marvin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Philadelphia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Faulk NNP I-NP I-PER O
quarterback NN I-NP O I-ORG
Ty NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Detmer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ricky NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Watters NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
NBA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
National NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
MIAMI NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ORLANDO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
CENTRAL NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
CHARLOTTE JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
INDIANA VBG I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
MIDWEST JJS I-NP O I-LOC
UTAH NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
DALLAS NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
DENVER NN I-NP I-ORG I-PER
VANCOUVER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
PORTLAND NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
GOLDEN NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
STATE NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SACRAMENTO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
PHOENIX NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BOSTON NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
DETROIT NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
PHOENIX NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
SACRAMENTO NNP I-NP I-LOC O
VANCOUVER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ANTONIO NNP I-NP I-LOC O
UTAH NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CHARLOTTE NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
PORTLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC O
INDIANA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
GOLDEN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
STATE NNP I-NP I-LOC O
ORLANDO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
LAKERS NNS I-NP I-LOC O
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
AMERICAN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
National NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Football NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
League NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
AMERICAN NNP I-NP I-MISC O
EASTERN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PA NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ENGLAND NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BUFFALO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
INDIANAPOLIS NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
MIAMI NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
CENTRAL NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
JACKSONVILLE JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
WESTERN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PA NNP I-NP O I-ORG
X-DENVER NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
EASTERN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PA NNP I-NP O I-ORG
DALLAS NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
WASHINGTON NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ARIZONA VBG I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
CENTRAL NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PA NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Y-GREEN NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
BAY NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
WESTERN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
DIVISION NNP I-NP O I-MISC
L NNP I-NP O I-ORG
T NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PF NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PA NNP I-NP O I-ORG
CAROLINA VBG I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
X NN I-NP O I-LOC
Y NNP I-NP O I-LOC
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
BALTIMORE VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
CINCINNATI NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
DENVER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
GREEN NNP I-NP I-LOC O
BAY NNP I-NP I-LOC O
JACKSONVILLE NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
HOUSTON NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NEW JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
ORLEANS NNS I-NP I-LOC O
PITTSBURGH NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
WASHINGTON NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
TAMPA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
BAY NNP I-NP I-LOC O
DALLAS NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ARIZONA NNP I-NP I-LOC O
BUFFALO NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
SEATTLE NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CAROLINA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
DETROIT NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
OAKLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NFL NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
AMERICAN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Football NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
League NN I-NP I-LOC O
37 CD I-NP O I-ORG
NCAA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
AMERICAN NNP I-NP O I-MISC
FOOTBALL-OHIO NNP I-NP I-MISC O
STATE NNP I-NP I-MISC O
PACE NNP I-NP I-PER O
LOMBARDI NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-PER
AWARD NNP I-NP I-MISC O
HOUSTON NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lombardi NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Award NNP I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Houston NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ohio NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
State NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Rose NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Bowl NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Arizona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
State NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
outdistanced VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Virginia NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Tech NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Cornell NNP I-NP I-PER O
offensive JJ I-NP O I-ORG
tackle NN I-NP O I-ORG
Juan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Roque NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jared NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tomich NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Lombardi NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Award NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Green NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Bay NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Packers NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
for IN I-PP O I-ORG
for IN I-PP O I-ORG
1. CD I-NP I-ORG O
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Japhet NNP I-NP I-PER O
N'Doram NNP I-NP I-PER O
Claude NNP I-NP I-PER O
Makelele NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jocelyn NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gourvennec NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Pignol NNP I-NP I-PER O
N'Gotty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fischer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Konterman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vegt NNP I-NP I-PER O
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Monaco NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Bordeaux NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
LEAGUE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Stickroth NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wosz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kirsten NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramelow NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bode NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bormirow JJ I-NP I-PER O
Karlsruhe NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Reich NNP I-NP I-PER O
Freiburg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Quarter-final JJ I-NP O I-LOC
WEAH NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
HEAD-BUTT NNP I-NP O I-ORG
DEPRIVES NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PORTUGAL JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
COSTA NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Georg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Weah NNP I-NP I-PER O
Costa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Paulinho NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Santos NNPS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Conceicao NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paulo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bento NNP O I-PER O
Oviedo NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Taira NNP I-NP I-PER O
Salamanca NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Paulo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Alves NNPS I-NP I-PER O
REAL NNP O I-ORG O
MADRID VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
and CC O O I-ORG
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Draw NN I-NP O I-LOC
Correct JJ I-ADJP O I-LOC
3-0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
20-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3-1 CD I-NP O I-LOC
3-2 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
25-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-0 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
50-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4-1 CD I-NP O I-LOC
4-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
50-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Draw NN I-NP O I-LOC
3-3 JJ I-ADVP O I-LOC
Double RB I-NP O I-PER
half-time NN I-NP O I-LOC
5-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Real NNP I-NP B-ORG I-ORG
14-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
28-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Barcelona NNP I-NP B-ORG I-ORG
5-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Draw NNP I-NP O I-ORG
4-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Draw NNP I-NP O I-ORG
11-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Draw NNP I-NP O I-ORG
25-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Real NNP I-NP B-ORG I-ORG
14-1 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
4-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Barcelona NNP I-NP B-ORG I-ORG
Barcelona NNP I-NP B-ORG I-ORG
9-2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Davor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Suker NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
5-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Pedrag NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mijatovic NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
7-1 JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
Raul NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gonzalez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
9-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
14-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
12-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
Amor NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
16-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
14-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
16-1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Manolo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sanchis NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
14-1 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Gheorghe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Popescu NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
16-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
JosepGuardiola NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
20-1 CD I-NP O I-PER
20-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
laPena SYM O I-PER I-LOC
20-1 CD I-NP O I-PER
25-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
Enrique NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
33-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
Sanz NNP I-NP I-PER O
AbelardoFernandez NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
40-1 JJ I-NP O I-PER
28-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
40-1 JJ I-NP O I-PER
33-1 NNP I-NP O I-PER
Ferrer NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
40-1 JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Chendo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Porlan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
33-1 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Miguel NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nadal NNP I-NP I-PER O
40-1 JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER O
SHOWCASE-FANS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
FACE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
BREATHALYSER NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TESTS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
stadium NN I-NP I-LOC O
Real NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Madrid-Barcelona NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Tickets NNS I-NP O I-LOC
SPANISH NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Athletic NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Bilbao NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Valladolid NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Valencia NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Tenerife NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Espanyol NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Oviedo NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Gijon NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Logrones NNS I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Zaragoza NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Sevilla NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Compostela RB I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hercules NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Extremadura NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
SPAIN VB I-VP I-LOC I-ORG
PICK NN I-NP O I-ORG
UNCAPPED NNP I-NP O I-ORG
ARMANDO NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Clemente NNP I-NP I-PER O
midfielder FW I-NP O I-ORG
Armando NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Alvarez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Armando NNP I-NP I-PER O
playmaker NN I-NP O I-ORG
Caminero NNP I-NP I-PER O
BOSS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
HAVELANGE NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
STANDS NNPS I-NP O I-ORG
WEAH PRP I-NP I-PER O
FIFA JJ I-NP I-ORG O
Havelange NNP I-NP I-PER O
personally RB I-VP O I-ORG
present VB I-VP O I-ORG
George NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Weah NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Weah NNP I-NP I-PER O
Costa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Fair NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Play NN I-NP O I-MISC
Havelange NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lisbon NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Costa JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Weah NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Weah NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Costa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Costa JJ I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Costa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Weah NNP I-NP I-PER O
Weah NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Europoean NNP I-NP I-MISC O
GUNMEN NNP I-NP O I-ORG
WOUND NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MANCHESTER NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
UNITED NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Two CD I-NP O I-ORG
Britons NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Mercedes NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Italian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Serie NNP I-NP B-MISC O
A NNP I-NP I-MISC O
fourth-placed JJ I-NP O I-ORG
represent VB I-VP O I-ORG
Led VBN I-VP O I-LOC
Igor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kolyvanov NNP I-NP I-PER O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Bottom NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Beiersdorfer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Daniele NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Carnasciali NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Lorenzo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Amoruso NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Emiliano NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bigica NNP I-NP I-PER O
attack-oriented JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Milan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rapajic NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Fausto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lazio NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Poor JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Roman JJ I-NP I-MISC I-PER
UEFA NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Cups NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Lazio NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Pierluigi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Casiraghi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nedved NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paolo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Negro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Abel NNP I-NP I-PER I-MISC
Balbo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Delvecchio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Totti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Can MD O O I-ORG
Liberian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Good JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Napoli NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
In-form NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Ayala NNP I-NP I-PER O
Verona NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Eugenio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Atlalanta NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Stanic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bravo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fabio NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cannavaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sensini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Atalanta NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Inzaghi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sampdoria NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
All-conquering VBG I-VP O I-ORG
field NN I-NP O I-ORG
Dimas NNP I-NP I-PER O
Piero NNP I-NP I-PER O
Croat NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Alen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boksic NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mancini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Laigle NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vicenza NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Full JJ I-NP O I-ORG
strength NN I-NP O I-ORG
Uruguayan NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Otero NNP I-NP I-PER O
Joceyln NNP I-NP I-PER O
Angloma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zamorano NNP I-NP I-PER O
EUROLEAGUE NNP I-NP I-MISC O
EuroLeague NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Charleroi NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Charleroi NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Charleroi NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Cleymans NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Stas NNP I-NP I-PER O
Harper NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Williams NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chadler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aisa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Group NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Koturovic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kinder NN I-NP O I-LOC
Zoran NNP I-NP I-PER O
Savic NNP I-NP I-PER O
EYLES NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mahindra NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
International NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Top-seeded JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Eyles NNPS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nicol NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Nicol NNP I-NP I-PER O
MAHINDRA NNP I-NP I-MISC O
INTERNATIONAL NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mahindra NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
International NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
squash NN I-NP O I-ORG
Nicol VB I-NP I-PER O
GUNMEN NNP I-NP O I-ORG
KILL MD I-VP O I-ORG
S.AFRICA NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
'S POS B-NP O I-ORG
ZULU NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
PROVINCE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
DURBAN NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Zulu NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Izingolweni NNP I-NP I-LOC O
KwaZulu-Natal JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Umkomaas NNPS I-NP I-LOC O
Bala NNP I-NP I-PER O
Naidoo NNP I-NP I-PER O
KwaZulu-Natal NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Zulu NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mangosuthu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Buthelezi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
HAVEL NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
PRAISES NNPS I-NP O I-ORG
CZECH VB I-VP I-MISC I-ORG
NATIVE CD I-NP O I-ORG
ALBRIGHT NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
AS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
FRIEND VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Klara NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Gajduskova NNP I-NP I-PER O
Czech NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Madeleine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Madeleine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
fine JJ I-NP O I-ORG
origins NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Marie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Korbelova NNP I-NP I-PER O
Czechoslovak JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Communists NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Czech JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soveit-bloc JJ I-NP I-MISC O
trans-Atlantic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Josef NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zieleniec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NN I-NP I-PER O
convinced VBN I-VP O I-ORG
advocate NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
enlargement NN B-NP O I-ORG
Czech JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Karel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kovanda NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mlada NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Fronta NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Dnes NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Czechs NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
AFTERNOON NNP I-NP O I-ORG
HEALINES NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Radio NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Romania NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hungarian NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Democratic NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
UDMR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Emil NNP I-NP I-PER O
Constantinescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Constantinescu NNP I-NP I-PER O
UDMR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Marko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bela NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timisoara NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Arad NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Oradea NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Sibiu NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CZECH NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Czech JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Civic NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ODS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ODS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Josef NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zieleniec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zieleniec NNP I-NP I-PER O
ODS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Brno NNP B-NP I-LOC O
ODS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Margaret NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thatcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zieleniec VBN I-VP I-PER I-LOC
post-Communist JJ I-NP I-MISC O
ODS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
centre-left JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Social NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Democrats NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
POLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
GOT NNP O O I-ORG
POST-WAR NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SWISS NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
ACCOUNTS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Grajewski NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jews NNPS I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Holocaust NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Two CD I-NP I-MISC O
Foreign NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Switzerland NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
stands VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Alfonse NNP I-NP I-PER O
D'Amato NNP I-NP I-PER O
German NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Warsaw NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Soviet-imposed JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Two CD I-NP I-MISC O
Holocaust JJ I-NP I-MISC O
FDP NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
INTERVIEW-ZYWIEC NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Silber NNP I-NP I-PER O
Polish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Zywiec NN I-NP I-ORG O
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zywiec NNP B-NP I-ORG O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Heineken NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Carlsberg NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Okocim NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SAB NNP O I-ORG O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
brewers NNS B-NP O I-ORG
Brewpole NNP I-NP I-ORG O
BV NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Elbrewery NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Company NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ltd. NNP I-NP I-ORG O
EB NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG O
CEFTA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Okocim NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Carlsberg NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Heineken NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Full NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Light NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heineken NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Van NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Boxmeer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zywiec NNP I-NP I-ORG O
HAVEL NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
HAS VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
TRAECHEOTOMY NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Ladlislav NNP I-NP I-PER O
Spacek NNP I-NP I-PER O
UK-US NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
UK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
DOT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Telkom NN I-INTJ I-ORG I-LOC
PT PRP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Telekomunikasi NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Indonesia NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Telkom NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Woman NN I-NP O I-LOC
N. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-PER
mortar NN I-NP O I-ORG
Belfast NNP I-NP I-LOC O
kitchen NN I-NP O I-ORG
wall NN I-NP O I-ORG
Security NN I-NP O I-ORG
American JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
alliance NN I-NP O I-ORG
trans-Atlantic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Monopolies NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP I-ORG O
Lang NNP I-NP I-PER O
trans-Atlantic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Lang NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Fair NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Trading NNP I-NP I-ORG O
BA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
AA NN I-NP I-ORG O
trans-Atlantic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Industry NN I-NP O I-ORG
Airways-American JJ I-NP I-MISC O
and CC O O I-ORG
drop NN I-NP O I-ORG
168 CD B-NP O I-ORG
slots NNS I-NP O I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-ORG O
British NNP I-NP I-ORG O
USAir NNP I-NP I-ORG O
trans-Atlantic JJ I-NP I-MISC O
and CC O O I-ORG
Dallas-Fort NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Worth NNP I-NP I-LOC O
London-to-Boston NNP I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Fair NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Trade NNP I-NP I-ORG O
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Lang NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Fair NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Trading NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Med JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Mediterranean JJ I-NP O I-LOC
cif NN I-NP O I-ORG
quotes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
+$0.50 CD I-NP O I-ORG
basis NN I-NP O I-ORG
Trades NNS I-NP O I-LOC
High JJ I-NP O I-ORG
sulphur NN I-NP O I-ORG
cracked VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Low NNP I-NP O I-ORG
sulphur NN I-NP O I-ORG
scooped VBD I-VP O I-ORG
New JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Sale NN I-NP I-ORG O
Grammar NNP I-NP I-ORG O
School NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Manchester NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Wales NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
grappled VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Cardiff NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Lanarkshire NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
office-Conservatives JJ I-NP I-MISC O
British NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Conservative JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Gorst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gorst NN I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Downing NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Gorst NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Before IN I-PP O I-ORG
Gorst NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
651-seat JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Gorst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gorst JJS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
bags NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Information NN I-NP O I-ORG
technology NN I-NP O I-ORG
firm NN I-NP O I-ORG
Private NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Finance NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Initiative NNP I-NP O I-ORG
EDS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Oceanic NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Control NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Centre NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Prestwick NNP I-NP I-LOC O
NATS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Europe NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
and CC O O I-ORG
North NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
America NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
+44-171-542 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Australia-West NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Indies NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Sherwin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shivnarine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chanderpaul NNP I-NP I-PER O
CONTRACT NNP I-NP O I-LOC
DATE NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Feb NN I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
79.94 CD I-NP O I-ORG
79.67 CD I-NP O I-ORG
75.55 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Mar NNP I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
76.37 CD I-NP O I-ORG
76.12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
72.02 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Apr NNP I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
74.13 CD I-NP O I-ORG
74.69 CD I-NP O I-ORG
70.59 CD I-NP O I-ORG
May NNP I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
76.51 CD I-NP O I-ORG
77.07 CD I-NP O I-ORG
72.97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Jun NN I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
77.53 CD I-NP O I-ORG
77.24 CD I-NP O I-ORG
73.17 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Jul JJ I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
74.45 CD I-NP O I-ORG
74.01 CD I-NP O I-ORG
69.95 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Aug VBG I-VP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
72.41 CD I-NP O I-ORG
72.07 CD I-NP O I-ORG
68.01 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sep NN I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
69.18 CD I-NP O I-ORG
69.24 CD I-NP O I-ORG
65.17 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Oct NNP I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
68.00 CD I-NP O I-ORG
68.05 CD I-NP O I-ORG
63.98 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Nov NNP I-NP O I-ORG
97 CD I-NP O I-ORG
68.00 CD I-NP O I-ORG
68.05 CD I-NP O I-ORG
63.98 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Manitoba NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Index NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Dec NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Manitoba NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Winnipeg NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Canadian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
West NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Coast NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Vessel NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Loadings NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Canadian NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
West NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Coast NNP I-NP O I-ORG
West NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Coast NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Thunder NNP I-NP I-LOC O
East NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Coast NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Port NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Loading NNP I-NP O I-ORG
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
timecharter NN I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
coal NN I-NP O I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
ore NN I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
ORE RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Maritime NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Queen NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
70,000 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Dampier NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kaohsiung NNP I-NP I-LOC O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Steel NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Desk NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
FIXTURES NNP I-NP O I-LOC
HEMISPHERE NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Danila NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
28.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
16/12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Caribs NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mobil NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Desk NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dirty JJ I-NP O I-LOC
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
MIDEAST NNP I-NP O I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
RED VBN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
SEA NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Thai NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Resource NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
264 CD I-NP O I-ORG
31/12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Ras NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Tanura NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Red NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Sea NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
W46.50 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
MEDITERRANEAN NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Lula NN I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-MISC O
25/12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sidi NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kreir NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Augusta NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
W100 NN I-NP O I-ORG
Spetses NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
139 CD I-NP O I-ORG
17/12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sidi NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Kreir NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Augusta NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
W97.50 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Mesipia NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
77.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
17/12 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bajaia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Fos NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
W105 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NYC NNP I-NP I-MISC O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
City NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
, , O I-ORG O
Euronotes NNS I-NP I-MISC O
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
City NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Joan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gralla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wall NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
St NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
speculates VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Fe NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Brendan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Intindola NNP I-NP I-PER O
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
unsolicited JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
suitor NN I-NP O I-ORG
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Nevada NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Busang NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Nevada NNP I-NP I-LOC O
South NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
America NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Homestake NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Homestake NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Albuquerque NNP I-NP I-LOC O
N.M. NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Nevada NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kazakstan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ghana NNP I-NP I-LOC O
PaineWebber NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Cohen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Homestake NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont-Santa NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Fe NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP B-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmonth NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Newmont NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Santa VB I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
Fe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
OAKLAND NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Curts NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cooke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cooke NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Zimbabwe NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
executes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Piniel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sindiso NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ncube NNP I-NP I-PER O
Multinational JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Lieutenant-General NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Maurice NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Baril NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Baril NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kabila NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kinshasa NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
opposes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
airdrops NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Canadian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Defence NN I-NP O I-ORG
Baril NNP I-NP I-PER O
Do VBP O O I-LOC
Chapter NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Chapter NNP I-NP O I-MISC
charter NN I-NP O I-ORG
Baril NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bukavu NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kindu NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kisangani NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Medecins NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
sans FW I-NP I-ORG O
Frontieres FW I-NP I-ORG O
Goma-Bukavu NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Walikale NNP I-NP I-LOC O
PORT JJ I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
LOUIS NNS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mauritian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Daniella NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Winds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Port NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
evacuates VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
UNHCR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Abdou NNP I-NP I-PER O
Diouf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moustapha NNP I-NP I-PER O
Niasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Diouf RB I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Franco-African JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Burkina NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Faso NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Diouf NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moustapha NNP I-NP I-PER O
Niasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ex-minister NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Kopessoua NNP I-NP I-PER O
Franco-African JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Burkina NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Faso NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Public NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Service NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dofara NNP I-NP I-PER O
interior NN I-NP O I-ORG
Grelombe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ange-Felix NNP I-NP I-PER O
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Grelombe NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Yakoma NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dofora NNP I-NP I-PER O
French-owned JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Yakomas NNS I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baya NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Roadblocks NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Shops NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Franco-African JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Chirac NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Burkina NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Faso NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Blaise NNP I-NP I-PER O
Compaore NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mali NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER O
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Church-led JJ I-NP O I-ORG
meadiation NN I-NP O I-ORG
Patasse NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Rebels NNS I-NP O I-ORG
accuse VBP I-VP O I-ORG
Patasse NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
tribalism NN I-NP O I-ORG
Mutineers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Codos NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Hospital NN I-NP O I-LOC
strongholds NNS I-NP O I-ORG
rained VBD I-VP O I-ORG
mortar NN I-NP O I-ORG
shells NNS I-NP O I-ORG
SAfrican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Mafikeng NNP I-NP I-LOC O
No DT I-NP O I-ORG
weather-related JJ I-NP O I-ORG
closures NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
CIS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Russian NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Skinheads NNS I-NP O I-ORG
attack VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Bratislava NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Rabbi NNP I-NP O I-ORG
rabbi NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Bratislava NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Baruch NNP I-NP I-PER O
Meyers NNP I-NP I-PER O
Meyers NNP I-NP I-PER O
Meyers NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Albanian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Buza NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Berisha NNP I-NP I-PER O
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Buza NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Qazim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gjonaj NNP I-NP I-PER O
Buza NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gjonaj NNP I-NP I-PER O
Polish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Pope NNP I-NP O I-PER
Pope NNP I-NP O I-PER
Warsaw NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pope NNP I-NP O I-PER
Warsaw NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
@ IN O O I-LOC
Russia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
warns VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Lynnley NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Browning NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Livshits NNP I-NP I-PER O
Norilsk NNP I-VP I-ORG O
Nickel NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Konstantin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Chernyshev NNPS B-NP I-PER O
Rinaco NNP B-NP I-ORG O
Plus NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Livshits NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Livshits NNPS I-NP I-PER O
0#NKEL.RUO CD I-NP O I-ORG
Christopher NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Granville NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Chernyshev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Entire RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
icy JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Far NNP I-NP O I-ORG
North NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Norilsk NN I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Livshits NNP I-NP I-PER O
telling VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNS I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Chernyshev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Krasnoyarsk NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Uneximbank NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Interrosimpex NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Uneximbank NN I-NP I-ORG O
Norilsk NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Estonian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
11-mo CD I-NP O I-ORG
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Madeleine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
First NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Igor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ivanov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russian-U.S. JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Ivanov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Albright NNP I-NP I-PER O
Russia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
opposes VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Soviet-led JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Warsaw NNP I-NP B-MISC I-ORG
Pact NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Russian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Yegor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stroyev NNP I-NP I-PER O
December NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Mikhail NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gorbachev NNP I-NP I-PER O
Surgeon NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Renat NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Akchurin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bomb VB I-VP O I-ORG
explodes VBZ B-VP O I-ORG
TASR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Frantisek NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gaulieder NNP I-NP I-PER O
Galanta NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Gaulieder NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Meciar NNP I-NP I-PER O
for IN I-PP I-ORG O
a DT I-NP I-ORG O
Democratic NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Slovakia NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
TASR NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Gaulieder NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Bomb VB I-VP O I-ORG
explodes VBZ B-VP O I-ORG
Kazanluk NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Violent JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Bombings NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Kazanluk NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Hungarian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Budapest NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bank NNP I-NP O I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Sandor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tolonics NNPS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sandor NNP I-NP I-PER O
Peto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Greenspan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Greenspan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jones NNP I-NP I-MISC I-PER
IPC NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Greenspan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yields NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Simec NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Sidek NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Sidek NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ADRs NNPS I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Heavyweights NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Televisa NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ponce NNP I-NP I-PER O
Santander NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ponce NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Plastic NN I-NP O I-LOC
Simona NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
de NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Logu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Plastic NN I-NP O I-LOC
Brazilians NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Farid NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hakme NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brazilian JJ I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Plastic NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SBCP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Our PRP$ I-NP O I-LOC
Hakme NNP I-NP I-PER O
Latin NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
America NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Ivo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pitangy NNP I-NP I-PER O
SBCP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hakme VB I-VP I-PER I-LOC
attributes NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Stomach NN I-NP O I-ORG
tucks NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Brazilians NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Vice-President NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Oswaldo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Saldanha NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Beauty NN I-NP O I-ORG
ideals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Plastic NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Claudia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Liz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saldanha NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Daily NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Avg NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Buenos NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Aires VBZ I-VP I-LOC I-ORG
Quequen VBN I-VP B-LOC I-ORG
Rosario NNP I-NP B-LOC I-ORG
Bahia NNP I-NP B-LOC I-ORG
Blanca NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Oats NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Wheat NN I-NP O I-ORG
121 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Maize NN I-NP O I-LOC
Maize NN I-NP O I-LOC
Sorghum NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Millet NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Soybeans NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Sunseeds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
+541 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Mexican JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Kenda NNP I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
Pacific NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Coast NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Pacific NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Coast NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Light NN I-NP O I-LOC
Baja NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
California NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Sinaloa NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Winds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Baja NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
California NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
peninsula NN I-NP O I-ORG
Sonora NNP I-NP I-LOC O
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
Cold JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Tamaulipas NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Winds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Tropical JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Quintana NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Roo NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Winds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Aspin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brazil NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
exam NN I-NP O I-ORG
cheats NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Brazilian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Seventy-seven JJ I-NP O I-LOC
SANTIAGO NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Finance NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Aninat NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aninat NNP I-NP I-PER O
Aninat NNP B-NP I-PER O
Aninat JJ I-ADJP I-PER I-LOC
Chilean JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Congress NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Congress NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Atwood NNP I-NP I-PER O
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timor NNP I-NP I-LOC O
East NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Timorese JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Roman NNP I-NP B-MISC I-ORG
Catholic NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dili NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
East NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Timorese-born NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timor NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Alatas NNS I-NP I-PER O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
the DT I-NP I-ORG O
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Horta NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Ramos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horta NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timor NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alatas NNP I-NP I-PER O
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pope NNP I-NP O I-PER
Belo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timor NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Hainan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
China NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Hainan JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Xinhua NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Qinglan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Wenchang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Government NN I-NP O I-ORG
disperses VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Burmese NN I-NP I-MISC O
Ranyon NNP I-NP I-ORG O
( ( O I-ORG O
Rangoon NN I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
) ) O I-ORG O
Insein JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Burmese NN I-NP I-MISC O
Vithoon NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Amorn NNP I-NP I-PER O
YIT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Aung NNP I-NP I-PER O
San NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
SLORC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Aung NNP I-NP I-PER O
San NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
NLD NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Yangon JJ I-NP I-LOC O
Suu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Union NNP I-NP O I-LOC
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ILO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ILO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bill NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ICFTU NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ILO NN I-NP I-ORG O
Hansenne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
pressured JJ I-VP O I-ORG
WTO NN I-NP I-ORG O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ICFTU JJ I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Jordan NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ICFTU NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ASEAN NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ILO JJ I-NP I-ORG O
ASEAN NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Brunei NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Philippines NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Vietnam NNP I-NP I-LOC O
ILO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ICFTU JJ I-NP I-ORG O
Eglin NNP I-NP I-PER O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ILO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
India NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
K.J. NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Matthew NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Asia NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Rubber NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Markets NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
meeting NN I-NP I-MISC O
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Matthew NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Natural JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Nishiyama NNP I-NP I-PER O
Comments NNS I-NP O I-LOC
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Japan NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Yasuo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Matsushita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eisuke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
high-ranking JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hank NNP I-NP I-PER O
Note VB I-VP I-PER O
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Note VB I-VP I-PER O
Takao NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sakoh NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Switzerland NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Market NN I-NP O I-ORG
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Adding VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Mr NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sakakibara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Matsushita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Matsushita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nihon NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Keizai NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Shimbun NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Yasuhito NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kawashima NNP I-NP I-PER O
Taisuke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Senior NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Lebanon NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
sentences NNS I-NP O I-ORG
pro-Israeli VB I-VP I-MISC I-ORG
Haitham NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Haddadin NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
capable JJ I-ADJP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
pressuring VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Lebanon NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Syrian-backed JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lebanese JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
citizens NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Israeli-held JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Christian-Shi'ite JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Moslem NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lebanese JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
patriot NN I-NP O I-ORG
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
SLA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Etian NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saqr NNP I-NP I-PER O
pro-Israeli JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Guardians NNP I-NP I-ORG O
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
the DT I-NP I-ORG O
Cedars NNPS I-NP I-ORG O
Christian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-PER
Saqr NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Lahd NNP I-NP I-PER O
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
w IN I-NP O I-ORG
Okla NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
steers VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Feedlots NNS I-NP O I-ORG
reporting VBG I-VP O I-ORG
moderate JJ I-NP O I-ORG
inquiry NN I-NP O I-ORG
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Steers NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Heifers NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Est JJS I-NP O I-LOC
CATTLE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
CALVES NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Friday NNP I-NP O I-ORG
12/06/96 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Week NN I-NP O I-LOC
Saturday NNP I-NP O I-ORG
12/07/96 NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Week NN I-NP O I-LOC
Same JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Period NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Same JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Period NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Percent NN I-NP O I-LOC
*1995 CD I-NP O I-ORG
totals NNS I-NP O I-ORG
NASS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
BALANCE NNP I-NP O I-PER
Hartford NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Conn NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CITY NN I-NP O I-LOC
HARTFORD NNP I-NP I-LOC O
CONNECTICUT NNP I-NP I-LOC O
GENERAL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
OBLIGATION NNP O O I-ORG
12/15/2000 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,250M CD I-NP O I-ORG
6.25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2001 CD I-NP O I-ORG
575M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.60 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2003 CD I-NP O I-ORG
265M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.40 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2004 CD I-NP O I-ORG
625M CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2005 CD I-NP O I-ORG
55M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.60 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2006 CD I-NP O I-ORG
145M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.70 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2007 CD I-NP O I-ORG
850M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.85 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2008 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,200M CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.95 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2009 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,240M CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2010 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,250M CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2011 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,240M CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2012 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,200M CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2013 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1,135M CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
12/15/2014 CD I-NP O I-ORG
850M CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Company NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Incorporated NNP I-NP I-ORG O
PaineWebber NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Incorporated NNP I-NP I-ORG O
NJ NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Florida NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Fourteen CD I-NP O I-LOC
Jr NNP I-NP O I-PER
Florida NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
electric JJ I-NP O I-ORG
chair NN I-NP O I-ORG
Lawhon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Florida NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lester NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lawhon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Arabic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Eugene NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Morris NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Allah NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Prison NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Yuhanna NNP I-NP I-PER O
Muhammed NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER O
Florida NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
electric JJ I-NP O I-ORG
chair NN I-NP O I-ORG
Prison NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mills NNP I-NP I-PER O
Circuit NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Mills NNPS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lester NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lawhon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lester NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Lawhon NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mills NNS I-NP I-PER O
Lawhon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Frederick NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mana NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Minn NNP I-NP B-LOC I-LOC
sales-USDA NN I-NP I-MISC O
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
steers VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Offerings NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Steers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Heifers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Carcass NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Basis NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Steers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Holstein NN I-NP O I-LOC
Holsteins NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Heifers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Wk VB I-VP O I-LOC
Man NN I-NP O I-PER
1996-12-06 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Darrel NNP I-NP I-PER O
Voeks NNP I-NP I-PER O
Outagmie NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
County NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Circuit NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Court NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Judge NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dennis NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Luebke NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Voeks NNS I-NP I-PER O
Voeks NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Voeks NNP I-NP I-PER O
Canadian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
) ) O O I-ORG
Statistics NNPS I-NP O I-ORG
Visible JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Supplies NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Farmers NNPS B-NP O I-ORG
Curr NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Wk NN I-NP O I-ORG
Wheat NN I-NP O I-ORG
4320.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3909.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
288.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6278.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Durum NN I-NP O I-ORG
1168.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1225.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
44.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
965.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Oats NNP I-NP O I-ORG
286.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
284.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
31.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
937.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Barley NNP I-NP O I-ORG
1074.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1104.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
178.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2531.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Rye NNP I-NP O I-ORG
44.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
86.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2.3 CD I-NP O I-ORG
108.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Flax NNP I-NP O I-ORG
165.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
181.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
14.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
231.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Canola NN I-NP O I-ORG
646.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
769.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
60.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1902.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Corn NN I-NP O I-ORG
79.6 CD O O I-ORG
163.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
95.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
7785.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
7724.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
629.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
13050.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Exports NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Domestic JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Curr NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Wk NN I-NP O I-ORG
YTD TO I-VP O I-ORG
Ago NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Curr NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Wk NN I-NP O I-ORG
YTD TO I-VP O I-ORG
Wheat NN I-NP O I-ORG
387.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4677.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4553.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
55.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1039.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Durum NN I-NP O I-ORG
129.0 CD B-NP O I-ORG
1515.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1220.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
75.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Oats NNP I-NP O I-ORG
40.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
561.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
391.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
149.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Barley NNP I-NP O I-ORG
110.8 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1203.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
506.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
48.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
941.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Rye NNP I-NP O I-ORG
4.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
60.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
57.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
10.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Flax RB I-NP O I-ORG
7.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
154.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
235.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
22.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Canola NNP I-NP O I-ORG
47.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
988.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
1135.5 CD I-NP O I-ORG
46.7 CD I-NP O I-ORG
894.9 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Corn NN I-NP O I-ORG
4.4 CD I-NP O I-ORG
15.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
87.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
0.6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
22.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
730.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
9176.1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8188.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
164.2 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3156.0 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Statistics NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Canada NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Oats NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Rye NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Flaxseed NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Canola NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Exports NNS I-NP O I-ORG
29,200 CD I-NP O I-ORG
17,200 CD I-NP O I-ORG
7,700 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Ago NNP I-NP O I-ORG
47,000 CD I-NP O I-ORG
24,300 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8,700 CD I-NP O I-ORG
8,200 CD I-NP O I-ORG
natgas NN I-NP O I-ORG
NEW NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
YORK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Henry NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Hub NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
natgas NNS I-NP O I-ORG
January NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Feb NN I-NP O I-LOC
Most JJS I-NP O I-PER
Weather NNP I-NP O I-ORG
NWS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Resistance NN I-NP O I-ORG
Midcontinent JJ I-NP O I-LOC
3.40s. CD I-NP O I-ORG
New NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
York NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NYMEX NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hub NNP I-NP O I-LOC
NYMEX NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Physical JJ I-NP O I-LOC
AECO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Permian NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
natgas NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Permian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
KCBT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
February NNP I-NP O I-LOC
East JJ I-NP O I-LOC
West NNP I-NP O I-LOC
NYMEX NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Physical JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Waha NNP I-NP I-LOC O
H NNP I-NP I-PER O
McCulloch NNP I-NP I-PER O
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
barges NNS I-NP O I-ORG
lightly RB I-VP O I-ORG
ST. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
LOUIS NNPS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
U.S. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
barge NN I-NP O I-ORG
St. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Merchants NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Exchange NNP I-NP O I-ORG
mid-Mississippi JJ I-NP I-MISC O
McGregor NNP I-NP I-PER O
mid-Mississippi JJ I-NP I-MISC O
CBOT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
Trade NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Receipts NNPS I-NP O I-LOC
Wheat NN I-NP O I-LOC
St. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
21,346 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Toledo NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
61,514 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Corn NN I-NP O I-LOC
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
78,056 CD I-NP O I-ORG
St. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
217,092 NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Toledo NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
285,505 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Oats NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Minneapolis NNS I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
306,364 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Soybeans NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Chicago NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
8,674 CD I-NP O I-ORG
St. NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Louis NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
253,821 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Toledo NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
64,334 CD I-NP O I-ORG
White NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
House NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Action NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Performance NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Ariz NNP I-NP I-LOC O
1996-12-06 CD I-NP O I-LOC
and CC O O I-ORG
Half NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
dog NN I-NP O I-ORG
bites NNS I-NP O I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
vet NN I-NP O I-ORG
CHICAGO NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Humane NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Society NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Cornwell NNP I-NP I-PER O
Glencoe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Animal NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hospital NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Columbus NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Let VB I-VP O I-LOC
Cornwell NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Don NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rieck NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rottweilers NNP I-NP I-MISC O
shepherds NNS I-NP I-MISC O
cocker NN I-NP I-MISC O
spaniels NNS I-NP I-MISC O
Dalmatians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Doberman NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Rottweilers NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Rieck NNP I-NP I-PER O
Minn NNP I-NP B-LOC I-LOC
tested- JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Steers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Reported VBN I-NP O I-LOC
Week NN I-NP O I-LOC
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
steers VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Seller JJR I-NP O I-LOC
Week NN I-NP O I-LOC
Sm NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Pd NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Lst VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Wk NNP I-NP O I-ORG
800 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sm NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Pd NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Lst VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Dressed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Basis NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Delivered NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dressed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Basis NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Steers NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dressed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Basis NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Heifers NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Four CD I-NP O I-MISC
Four CD I-NP O I-MISC
Kofi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Annan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ghana NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ahmedou NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ould NNP I-NP I-PER O
Abdallah NNP I-NP I-PER O
Amara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Essy NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hamid NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Algabid NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Niger NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
the DT I-NP I-ORG O
Representatives NNS I-NP O I-ORG
missions NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Ghana NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Niger NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Paolo NNP B-NP I-PER O
Fulci NNP I-NP I-PER O
Garba NNP I-NP I-PER O
185-members JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Hooded VBN I-VP O I-LOC
Pamplona NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Herri NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Batasuna NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mussolini NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
granddaughter NN I-NP O I-ORG
rejoins NNS I-NP O I-ORG
far-right JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Alessandra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mussolini NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Mussolini NNP I-NP I-PER O
far-right JJ I-NP O I-ORG
AN DT I-NP I-ORG O
AN NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Gianfranco NNP B-NP I-PER O
Fini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fini NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
radio NN I-NP O I-ORG
RAI NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mussolini NNP I-NP I-PER O
Giuseppe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tatarella NNP I-NP I-PER O
AN DT I-NP I-ORG O
Mussolini JJ I-ADJP I-PER I-LOC
AN NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mussolini NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
AN DT I-NP I-ORG O
neo-fascist NN I-NP O I-ORG
MS-Fiamma NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Two CD I-NP I-MISC O
German NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Santa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Santa NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Claus NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Hanover NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Milan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Europe NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Agreement NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Hindu NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Hindu NN I-NP I-MISC O
Hindu NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
nationalist NN I-NP O I-ORG
BJP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
pro-Hindu JJ I-NP I-MISC O
BJP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Suraj NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bhan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ayodhya NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Hindu-Moslem JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Indian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
BJP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hindus NNP B-NP I-MISC O
Rama NNP I-NP I-PER O
BJP NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Indian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
STEEL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
OUTPUT NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Crude JJ I-NP O I-ORG
petroleum NN I-NP O I-ORG
2,557 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2,832 CD I-NP O I-ORG
15,838 CD I-NP O I-ORG
LUXEMBOURG NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
CHRISTMAS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Brussels NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
+32 CD I-NP O I-ORG
London NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
coal NN I-NP O I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
ore NN I-NP O I-ORG
COAL NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Lantau NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Peak NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Hay NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Point NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Newcastle NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
Kaohsiung NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
20-30/1 CD I-NP O I-ORG
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Steel NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Royal NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Clipper NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Fos NNS I-NP I-LOC O
Coe NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP I-ORG O
Clerici NNP I-NP I-ORG O
ORE RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
IMC NNP I-NP O I-ORG
TBN NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Dampier NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kaohsiung NNP I-NP I-LOC O
5.25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
fio NN I-NP O I-ORG
35,000 CD I-NP O I-ORG
shinc JJ I-NP O I-ORG
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Steel NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
UK NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
bookmakers NNS I-NP O I-ORG
lengthen VBP I-VP O I-ORG
Conservative JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Conservative JJ I-NP I-MISC O
High-flying VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Returns NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Treasuries NNPS I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Bunds NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Spanish JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Returns NNS I-NP O I-LOC
basket NN I-NP O I-ORG
OPEC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
OPECNA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
OPEC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Saharan NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Blend NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Minas NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Bonny NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Light NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Arabian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Light NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Dubai NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Tia NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Juana NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Isthmus NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major JJ I-NP I-PER O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Newfoundland NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Newfoundland NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Stephenville NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Newfoundland NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Learjet NNP I-NP I-MISC O
36 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Snow NNP I-NP I-PER O
Snow NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Snow NNP I-NP I-PER O
Grand NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Rapids NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Stephenville NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Shannon NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Stephenville NNP I-NP I-LOC O
negotiators NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Israeli JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Especially RB I-ADJP O I-LOC
Osama NNP I-NP I-PER O
el-Baz NN I-NP I-PER O
Palestinian NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Abdel-Rahman NNP I-NP I-PER O
Abdel-Rahman NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Turkey NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
hindered VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Damascus NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
denies VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
aiding VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Kesers NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karabuluts NNP I-NP I-PER O
Texas NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
/ SYM O O I-ORG
w IN I-NP O I-ORG
Okla NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
steers VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Feedlots NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Wk VB I-VP O I-LOC
Slaughter NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Steers NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Pen NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Select NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
week NN I-NP O I-LOC
Steers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Heifers NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Delphis NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hanover NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Delphis NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Hanover NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Aaa JJ I-ADJP O I-LOC
1997 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3.50 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3.60* CD I-NP O I-ORG
3.70 CD I-NP O I-ORG
3.75 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.00 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.00 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2001 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.20 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.20 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.35 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.40 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.65 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.65 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.00 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2006 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.70 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.70 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.85 CD I-NP O I-ORG
4.85 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2011 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.15 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.15 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2016 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.35 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.30 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.50 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.45 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.80 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.75 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6.10 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2021 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.45 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.40 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.60 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.55 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.90 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.85 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6.20 CD I-NP O I-ORG
2026 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.50 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.45 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.65 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.60 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.95 CD I-NP O I-ORG
5.90 CD I-NP O I-ORG
6.25 CD I-NP O I-ORG
*from NN I-NP O I-LOC
ACCESS NN I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
NYMEX NNP I-NP I-MISC O
ACCESS NNS I-NP I-MISC O
NYMEX NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Front-month JJ I-NP O I-ORG
heating NN I-NP O I-ORG
ACCESS NNP I-NP I-MISC O
NYMEX JJ I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
January NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Brinkerhoff NNP I-NP I-PER O
Los NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Angeles NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
bureau NN I-NP O I-ORG
Burns NNP I-NP I-PER O
Burns NNP I-NP I-PER O
Burns NNP I-NP I-PER O
Korydallos NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Olympic NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Tunis NNP O I-LOC O
Pan NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
bombmaker NN I-NP O I-PER
Korydallos NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Pan NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
American NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
airliner NN I-NP O I-ORG
approaching VBG I-VP O I-ORG
Athens NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
School NNP I-NP O I-LOC
N.M. NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Mike NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cito NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Albuquerque NNP I-NP I-LOC O
sharpened VBN I-NP O I-ORG
chin NN I-NP O I-ORG
strap JJ I-NP O I-ORG
buckles NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Cito NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cito NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Cito NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cyberspace NN I-NP O I-ORG
squabbles NNS I-NP O I-ORG
overshadow NN I-NP O I-ORG
copyright NN I-NP O I-ORG
Elif NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Kaban NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cyberspace NN I-NP O I-ORG
squabbles NNS I-NP O I-ORG
overshadowed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
frustrated JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Western JJ I-NP O I-ORG
delegate NN I-NP O I-ORG
Washington-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Consumer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Project NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Supporters NNS I-NP O I-LOC
century-old JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Berne NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Convention NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Gundegma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jargalshaihan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ulan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bator NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Alexander NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bavykin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pearl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Internet NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
technology NN I-NP O I-ORG
Network NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Internet NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
everyday JJ I-NP O I-ORG
U.S.-based JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Italy NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
evacuates VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Europeans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Garamba NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ugandan NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Kampala NNP B-NP I-LOC O
Zaireans NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Moroccan NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Benchaou NNP I-NP I-PER O
Benchaou NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Caledonia NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Benchaou NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moslem NNP I-NP B-MISC I-MISC
Italian NNP I-NP I-MISC O
MANTUA NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Italian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Addressing VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
League NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER O
Scalfaro NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Mantua NNP I-NP I-LOC O
League NNP I-NP I-LOC I-MISC
Italia NNP I-NP I-LOC O
League NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
River NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Venice NNP I-NP I-LOC O
of IN I-PP I-LOC O
Radiometer NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Wednesday NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Soeren NNP I-NP I-PER O
Linding NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jakobsen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Moslem NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Moslem NN I-NP I-MISC O
Blida NNP I-NP I-LOC O
APS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Belgian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Barcelona NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Port NN I-NP O I-LOC
German NNP I-NP I-MISC O
German JJ I-NP I-MISC O
DKV NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Imports NNS I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
1.04 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Colombia NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
shipped VBD I-VP O I-ORG
198,226 CD I-NP O I-ORG
bags NNS I-NP O I-ORG
El NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Salvador NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
160,553 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Hamburg NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Muenchener NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
European NNP I-NP I-ORG O
languages NNS I-NP O I-ORG
offcial JJ I-NP O I-ORG
European JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Brussels NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
John NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Lewis NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
UK NNP I-NP I-ORG I-PER
Partnership NNP I-NP O I-PER
Waitrose JJ I-NP I-ORG O
Timah VBN I-VP I-ORG I-LOC
British JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Euro-sceptic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Euro-sceptic NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Conservative JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Member NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Marlow NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cabinet NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Marlow NNP I-NP I-PER O
Newsnight NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Kenneth NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Marlow NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Major NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
pro-European NN I-NP I-MISC O
Heseltine NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pro-European NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Conservative JJ I-NP B-MISC I-ORG
MP NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Edwina NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Currie NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Clarke NNP I-NP I-PER O
Court NNP I-NP O I-ORG
ejects VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Hunt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Laurie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brereton NNP I-NP I-PER O
Accordingly RB I-ADVP O I-LOC
Pamela NNP I-NP I-PER O
O'Neil NNP I-NP I-PER O
One CD I-NP O I-MISC
Australian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Paul NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Crofts NNPS I-NP I-PER I-ORG
New NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
South NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Wales NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Supreme NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Leszic NNP I-NP I-PER O
Betcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Grove NNP I-NP I-PER O
Crofts NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Grove NNP I-NP I-PER O
Grove NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Betcher NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bolger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nats NNP I-NP I-PER O
NZ NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
First NNP I-NP O I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Nat NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lab NNP I-NP I-PER O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
negotiators NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Helen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Clark NNP I-NP I-PER O
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
MP NNP I-NP O I-PER
Langmore NNP I-NP I-PER O
Australian JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Langmore NNP I-NP I-PER O
office NN I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Halverson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Halverson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vance NNP I-NP I-PER O
Langmore NNP I-NP I-PER O
Capital NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Territory NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Halverson NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Langmore NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Inge NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kaul NNP I-NP I-PER O
Langmore NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Labor NN I-NP O I-ORG
Keating NNP I-NP I-PER O
Canberra NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bureau NNP I-NP O I-ORG
61-6 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Burmese NN I-NP I-MISC O
YIT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
YIT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Shwe NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Dagon NNP I-NP I-LOC O
SLORC NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Thai NNP I-NP I-MISC O
detailed VBN B-NP O I-ORG
rice NN I-NP O I-ORG
loading NN I-NP O I-ORG
Vessel NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Iran NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Sabr NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
19/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Princess NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-MISC I-ORG
Loine NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
19/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Deligst NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
20/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Seagramd JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
ace NN I-NP O I-ORG
20/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Lucky JJ I-ADJP I-MISC I-ORG
Emdldm NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
20/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sangthai NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Glory NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
22/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Myos NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Yang NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Budisuryana NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
22/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
King NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Ace NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
22/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Tong NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Shun NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
25/11/96 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Vietnam NNP B-NP I-LOC O
But CC O I-MISC O
Bangkok NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
Chinese JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Wen NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hui NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bao NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Heavy NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Foreign JJ I-NP O I-ORG
Guilin NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Guilin NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Guangxi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Port NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Office NNP I-NP O I-ORG
of IN I-PP I-ORG O
China NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Guangxi NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Japan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Shimpei NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nukaya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nukaya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sangetsu NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Net JJ I-NP O I-ORG
6.20 CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Busang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Arasu NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Canada NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
and CC O O I-ORG
Busang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Toronto NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Toronto NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mines NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC O I-ORG O
Busang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kalimantan NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Busang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Busang NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Mines NNP I-NP I-ORG O
and CC I-NP I-ORG O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ministry NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ministry NNP I-NP O I-ORG
's POS B-NP O I-ORG
Umar NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Busang NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Umar NN I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Busang VBG I-NP I-ORG O
Bre-X NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
PT NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Panutan NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Duta NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Panutan NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Group NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Sigit NNP I-NP I-PER O
Harjojudanto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Panutan NNP B-NP I-PER O
Busang NNP B-NP I-ORG O
of IN I-PP O I-ORG
Suharto NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Siti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hardianti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rukmana NNP I-NP I-PER O
Honda NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
RV NN I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
exceeds VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
S-MX NNP I-NP I-MISC O
S-MX FW I-NP I-MISC O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NN I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Desmond NNP I-NP I-PER O
Supple NNP I-NP I-PER O
I.D.E.A NNP I-NP I-ORG O
American JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
teenager NN I-NP O I-ORG
then-U.S. JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Trade NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Representative NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Mickey NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kantor NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Derek NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
da NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cunha NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ISEAS NNP I-NP I-ORG O
prestige NN I-NP O I-ORG
Singapore NNP B-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Tan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kong NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Yam NNP I-NP I-PER O
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
General NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Agreement NNP I-NP I-MISC O
on IN I-PP I-MISC O
Tariffs NNP I-NP I-MISC O
and CC I-NP I-MISC O
Trade NNP I-NP I-MISC O
GATT NNP I-NP I-MISC O
hailed VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Singapore NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Supple NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
West NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Supple NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Tan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Singaporean NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Tan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Supple NNS I-NP I-PER I-LOC
WTO NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Japan NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
NTT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
NTT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
NTT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Posts NNPS I-NP O I-ORG
and CC I-NP O I-ORG
Telecommunications NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Hisao NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horinouchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
NTT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Horinouchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horinouchi NNP I-NP I-PER O
NTT NNP I-NP I-ORG O
launches VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
Asian JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Dutch JJ I-NP I-MISC O
BILO NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BILO NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Malysia NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kuala NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Lumpur NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Johor NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Bahru NNP I-NP I-LOC O
BILO NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Ahold NNP I-NP I-ORG O
TOPS NNP B-NP I-MISC O
Ahold NN I-NP I-ORG O
TOPS NNP I-NP I-MISC O
BILO NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Ahold NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ahold NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Ahold NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-WOMEN JJ I-NP O I-ORG
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
WORLD NN I-NP I-MISC O
SUPER NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Profile NN I-NP O I-LOC
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Age NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Nation NN I-NP O I-LOC
Previous JJ I-NP O I-MISC
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lillehammer NNP I-NP I-LOC O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-WOMEN JJ I-NP O I-ORG
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
WORLD NN I-NP I-MISC O
SUPER NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Provisional JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pernila NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER O
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gerg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Isolde FW I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warwara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zelenskaja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Madlen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brigger-Summermatter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Florence NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Masnada NNP I-NP I-PER O
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
10= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Martina NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ertl NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
10= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Stefanie NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Schuster NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bibiana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Perez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
14. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sybille NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brauner NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Katharina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gutensohn NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leatitia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dalloz NNP I-NP I-PER O
17. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Renate NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
18. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Marianne NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brechu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zurbriggen NNP I-NP I-PER O
20. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Spela NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bracun NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
21. NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Shannon NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nobis NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
22= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Regine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cavagnoud NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
22= NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Anita NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Wachter NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
24. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Megan JJ I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gerety NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
25. CD I-NP O I-PER
Lindh NNP I-NP I-PER O
26= NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Catherine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Borghi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
26= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Michaela NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Dorfmeister NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
28. NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Alexandra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Meissnitzer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
29. CD O O I-ORG
Ingeborg VBG I-VP I-PER I-ORG
Helen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Marken NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
30. NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Monika NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tschirky NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-GLADISHIVA NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
SUPER NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Svetlana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Super NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Pernilla NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER O
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER O
JCPENNEY NNP I-NP I-MISC O
TARPON NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
SPRINGS NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Florida NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
JCPenney NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Innisbrook NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Hilton NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Resort NNP I-NP I-LOC O
PGA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
LPGA NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Hurst NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hulbert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kelli NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kuehne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tiger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Woods NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Beth NNP I-NP I-PER O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-WOMEN JJ I-NP O I-ORG
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
DOWNHILL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
WINNER NNP I-NP O I-ORG
PROFILE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Profile NN I-NP O I-LOC
Renate VB I-VP I-PER O
Goetschl NN I-NP I-PER O
Age NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Nation NN I-NP O I-LOC
Lillehammer NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Norway NNP I-NP B-LOC I-LOC
Flachau NNP I-NP I-LOC O
1993 CD I-NP I-MISC O
Europa NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-WOMEN JJ I-NP O I-ORG
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
WORLD NN I-NP I-MISC O
Downhill NNP I-NP O I-LOC
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Renate NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER O
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pernilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zurbriggen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Haeusl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Meissnitzer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Isolde FW I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ingeborg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Helen NNP I-NP I-PER O
10= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Megan JJ I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gerety NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
10= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Warwara NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zelenskaja NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
10= CD I-NP O I-LOC
Masnada NNP I-NP I-PER O
13= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Picabo NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Street NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
13= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Stefanie NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Schuster NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Vogt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bibiana NNP I-NP I-PER O
Perez NNP I-NP I-PER O
17. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Hilde NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gerg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
19= CD I-NP O I-PER
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER O
19= CD I-NP O I-PER
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
19= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Regine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cavagnoud NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Pernilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hide NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gerg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Anita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wachter NNP I-NP I-PER O
Isolde FW I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zurbriggen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warwara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zelenskaja NNP I-NP I-PER O
8= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Renate NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
8= NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
11. CD I-NP O I-LOC
Masnada NNP I-NP I-PER O
12. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Deborah NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Compagnoni NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ertl NNP I-NP I-PER O
14. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Alexandra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Meissnitzer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Urska NNP I-NP I-PER O
Horvat NNP I-NP I-PER O
16= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Claudia NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Riegler NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
16= NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Sabina NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Panzanini NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stefanie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schuster NNP I-NP I-PER O
Vogt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Super NNP I-NP I-MISC O
G NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Pernilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gerg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Svetland NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER O
Warwara NNP I-NP I-PER O
Zelenskaja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Florence NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Masnada NNP I-NP I-PER O
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Isolde FW I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER O
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ertl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Anita NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wachter NNP I-NP I-PER O
11. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zurbriggen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Madlen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brigger-Summermatter NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12= CD I-NP O I-PER
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
12= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Katharina NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gutensohn NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Stefanie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schuster NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leatitia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dalloz NNP I-NP I-PER O
17. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bibiana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Perez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
18= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Miriam NNP B-NP I-PER I-ORG
Vogt NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
18= CD I-NP O I-ORG
Marianne NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brechu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
20. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Alexandra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Meissnitzer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Nation NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
's POS B-NP I-MISC O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-WOMEN JJ I-NP O I-ORG
'S VBZ I-VP O I-ORG
WORLD NN I-NP I-MISC O
Provisional JJ I-NP O I-LOC
Renate NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER O
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER O
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Isolde FW I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Meissnitzer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Megan JJ I-NP I-PER O
Gerety NN I-NP I-PER O
Vogt NNP I-NP I-PER O
Stefanie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schuster NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ingeborg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Helen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Marken NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Florence NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Masnada NNP I-NP I-PER O
Haeusl NNP I-NP I-PER O
11. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Heidi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zurbriggen NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
12. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Warwara NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zelenskaja NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER O
14. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Hilde NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gerg NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
15. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Martina NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Ertl NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Pernilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wiberg NNP I-NP I-PER O
17. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Svetlana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Gladishiva NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
18. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Anita NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Wachter NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Spela NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bracun NNP I-NP I-PER O
20. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Regine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Cavagnoud NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
21. CD I-NP O I-PER
Pace NNP I-NP I-PER O
22. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Bibiana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Perez NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
23. CD I-NP O I-PER
Lindh NNP I-NP I-PER O
24. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Catherine NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Borghi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
25. NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Carole NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Montillet NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
26. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Brigitte NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Obermoser NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
27. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Sybille NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brauner NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
28. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Grete NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Stroem NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
29. CD I-NP O I-ORG
Patrizia NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bassis NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
30. NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Alessandra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Merlin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
NORDIC NNP I-NP O I-MISC
Vadim NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sashurin NNP I-NP I-PER O
rounds NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Frode NNP I-NP I-PER O
Andresen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ole JJ I-NP I-PER O
Einar NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bjorndalen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fischer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ricco NNP I-NP I-PER O
Gross NNP I-NP I-PER O
Fischer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Muslimov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sashurin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Melnik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Paramygina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Belorus NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Gunn NNP I-NP I-PER O
Andreassen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Simone NNP I-NP I-PER O
Greiner-Petter-Memm NNP I-NP I-PER O
Petra NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Behle NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Behle NN I-NP I-PER O
Paramygina NNP I-NP I-PER O
Greiner-Petter-Memm NNP I-NP I-PER O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-GOETCHL NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Renate NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Goetschl NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Katja NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Seizinger NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Islode NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kostner NNP I-NP I-PER O
BOBSLEIGH-SHIMER NNP I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
PILOTS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Brian NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shimer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
piloted VBD I-VP O I-ORG
Lying VBG I-VP O I-LOC
Shimer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Guenther NNP I-NP I-PER O
Tartaglia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Canada NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I NNP I-NP I-ORG O
Lueders NNPS I-NP I-PER O
MacEachern NNP I-NP I-PER O
cup NN I-NP I-MISC O
Canadians NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
Altenberg NNP I-NP I-LOC O
La NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Plagne NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
USA NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Herberich NNP I-NP I-PER O
SKIING-CHINESE JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
MAKE VB I-VP O I-ORG
PROMISING NN I-NP O I-ORG
FREESTYLE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING NNP I-NP O I-ORG
DEBUT NN I-NP O I-ORG
Tignes NNS I-NP I-LOC O
Cuo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nannan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Alexis NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Foucras NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Foucras NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bean NNP I-NP I-PER O
Veronica NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Brenner NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tignes NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Swiss JJ I-NP I-MISC O
Karin NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Kuster NNP I-NP I-PER O
Evelyne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leu NNP I-NP I-PER O
United NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
States NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
III NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Shimer NNP I-NP I-PER O
minute NN I-NP O I-ORG
45.91 CD B-NP O I-ORG
Italy NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Guenther NN I-NP I-PER O
Tartaglia NNP I-NP I-PER O
Canada NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Lueders NNP I-NP I-PER O
MacEachern NNP I-NP I-PER O
German JJ I-NP I-ORG I-MISC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Sepp NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dostthaler NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lebsa NNP I-NP I-PER O
Switzerland NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Reto NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goetschi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Guido NNP I-NP I-PER O
Acklin NNP I-NP I-PER O
Germany NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
III NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Wiese NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jakobs NNP I-NP I-PER O
Czech NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Republic NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Dzmura NNP I-NP I-PER O
Polomsky NNP I-NP I-PER O
1:46.06 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Austria NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Hubert NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schoesser NNP I-NP I-PER O
Britain NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Olsson NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ward NNP I-NP I-PER O
53.29 CD I-NP O I-LOC
United NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
States NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
I PRP B-NP I-ORG O
Herberich NNP I-NP I-PER O
Garrett NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hines NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Austria NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
III NNP I-NP I-ORG I-LOC
Conti NNP I-NP I-PER O
Georg NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kuttner NNP I-NP I-PER O
53.04). CD I-NP O I-LOC
WOOLMER NN I-NP I-PER O
KANPUR NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kanpur NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Kanpur NNP I-NP I-LOC O
South JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
African JJ I-NP I-MISC I-ORG
Greig NNP I-NP I-PER O
United NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Province NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Uttar NNP I-NP I-LOC O
Ranji NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Trophy NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Kanpur NNP I-NP I-LOC O
India-South NNP I-NP I-MISC O
Africa NNP I-NP I-MISC I-LOC
FREESTYLE NNP I-NP O I-MISC
freestyle JJ I-NP O I-ORG
skiing NN I-NP O I-ORG
aerials NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Alexis NNP I-NP I-PER O
Blanc NNP I-NP I-PER O
Foucras NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bean NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bergoust NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rijavec NNP I-NP I-PER O
Mikhailov NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ales NNPS I-NP I-PER O
Valenta NNP O I-PER O
Capicik NNP I-NP I-PER O
Trace NNP I-NP I-PER O
Worthington NNP I-NP I-PER O
Dmitri NNP B-NP I-PER O
Dashinski NNP I-NP I-PER O
Veronica NN I-NP I-PER O
Brenner NNP I-NP I-PER O
Karin NNP I-NP I-PER I-LOC
Kuster NNP I-NP I-PER O
Evelyne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Leu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jacqui NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marie NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lindgren NNP I-NP I-PER O
Cuo NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nannan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hilde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Synnove NNP I-NP I-PER O
Lid NNP I-NP I-PER O
SKI NNS I-NP O I-MISC
JUMPING-LEADING NN I-NP O I-MISC
Takanobu NNP I-NP I-PER O
Okabe NNP I-NP I-PER O
145.4 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Kazuyoshi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Funaki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Goldberger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thoma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ari-Pekka NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nikkola NNP I-NP I-PER O
Reinhard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schwarzenberger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Noriaki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kasai NNP I-NP I-PER O
Hiroya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saitoh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jani NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soininen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kristian JJ I-NP I-PER O
Brenden NNP I-NP I-PER O
Thoma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Brenden JJ I-NP I-PER O
Goldberger NNP I-NP I-PER O
Okabe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Funaki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Saitoh NNP I-NP I-PER O
Espen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bredesen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Nikkola NNP I-NP I-PER O
Soininen NNP I-NP I-PER O
Primoz NNP I-NP I-PER O
Peterka NNP I-NP I-PER O
TEMBAU NN I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
DENPASAR NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Bali NNP I-NP I-LOC O
semifinals NNS I-NP O I-LOC
Sun NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jun NNP I-NP I-PER O
Budi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kusuma NNP I-NP I-PER O
Susi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Susanti NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Camilla NNP I-NP I-PER O
11-3 CD I-NP O I-LOC
Ye NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Zhaoying NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
SPEED JJ I-NP O I-ORG
SKATING-RESULTS NNS I-NP O I-ORG
Horii NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Manabu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jaegal NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sung-Yeol NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Grunde NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Njos NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shimizu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hiroyasu NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sergey NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Klevchenya NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Yamakage NN I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hiroaki NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Casey NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Fitzrandolph NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sylvain NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Bouchard NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kim NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Yoon-man NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Inoue NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Junichi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Xuc NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Rulhong NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Svetlana NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jhurova NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Franziska NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Schenk NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Okazaki NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Tomomi NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Shimazaki NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Kyoko NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Marianne NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Timmer NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Jin NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Hua NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Alena NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Koroleva NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Chris NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Witty NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Anke NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Baler NNP I-NP I-PER I-ORG
Sylvain NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bouchard NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sergey NNP I-NP I-PER O
Klevchenya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Jan NNP I-NP I-PER O
Bos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Grunde NNP I-NP I-PER O
Njos NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kyou-hyuk NNP I-NP I-PER O
Inoue NNP I-NP I-PER O
Junichi NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yoon-man NNP I-NP I-PER O
Wotherspoon NNP I-NP I-PER O
Miyabe NNP I-NP I-PER O
Yasunori NNP I-NP I-PER O
Franziska NNP I-NP I-PER O
Schenk NNP I-NP I-PER O
Kusunose NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shiho NNP I-NP I-PER O
Marianne NNP I-NP I-PER O
Timmer NNP I-NP I-PER O
Anka NNP I-NP I-PER O
Baier NNP I-NP I-PER O
Becky NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sundstrom NNP I-NP I-PER O
Shimazaki NNP I-NP I-PER O
Ravllova NNP I-NP I-PER O
Sammiya NNP I-NP I-PER O
Eriko NNP I-NP I-PER O
Witty NNP I-NP I-PER O
Xue NNP I-NP I-PER O
Rulhong NNP I-NP I-PER O
ALPINE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
SKIING-OFFICIALS NNP I-NP O I-ORG
HOPE NNP I-NP O I-ORG
Whistler NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Mountain NNP I-NP I-LOC I-ORG
Zobel NNP I-NP I-PER O
PREMIER NNPS I-NP I-MISC O
